[Music]
I'm watching the the video of trump
grabbing his ear and thinking that's
when I slip my hand into his pocket and
take his wallet like I that's my
qualification we are going to have if he
were to go down we run up his credit
cards immediately and by the way yeah
we're going to have a former legendary
CIA agent John kyaku who was also in
prison like you but he was only in there
for 2 years put in there by the CIA um
oh he was oh okay yeah not like in
another country in the united states in
the United States oh that's nice yes
exactly he what did you do for that what
did you do that he uh well he was he was
um he was one of the guys responsible
for taking down one of the top guys in
al-Qaeda named Abu Zaba and he was a
part of a raid that captured this guy
and killed eventually killed uh no he's
in Guana they never killed him but he
the story about how he captured the guy
is crazy in I think it was
Pakistan and uh J's been through a lot
of [__] and eventually that's when the
enhanced interrogation [__] happened
started happening with the CIA where
they set up these black sites around the
world to basically torture people and
get uh information from
terrorists and John was blamed for it
cuz because he was the guy inside the
CIA complaining about it like why are we
doing this this is against the law this
violates the Geneva Convention right and
they're like stop bitching John stop
bitching and then
um somehow it came out and a reporter
contacted him from I think it was ABC
and said John um bush is on TV saying
yeah look there's the photo of the super
bullet yeah bush bush was on TV
basically saying that um talking about
the enhanced interrogation stuff and
saying that there was a CIA operative um
who leaked it and then
John thought he was talking about him so
John's like I'm going to go on live TV
and talk about it so John like went on
TV and blew out the blew up the whole
enhanced interrogation [__] the CIA was
doing and then they got him for
Espionage something like that some
[__] crime put him in
prison what is going on but John knows a
lot about this stuff and essentially So
like um Julian's been talking to his
paramilitary folks and I've talked to a
couple guys and um you know the one
thing that seems to be insane about
about this whole thing is that theying
didn't put anybody on those roofs that
were 300 feet 1 15 yards away and um as
we sit here in our air conditioned room
with our microphones we can you know
yeah we can tell everything we
could exactly critique what they did
wrong and uh let them know that they
need to be better yeah this is the V
this is the video it didn't have all
that [__] around it though like it was a
very much clearer video I think
but yeah watch this head tilt yeah that
would have boom right there how crazy is
that dude I tell you what that would
have done it would have if it hadn't
killed him it had taken him out of the
race I'll tell you that yeah oh yeah I
mean that would have took out his whole
visual cortex of his brain yeah I think
he would have been a vegetable that's
not good if it didn't kill him it
definitely would have [__] him up
permanently yeah yeah to be honest with
it let's face it the bullet prob killed
him it probably would have gone through
the initial it would have gone right
through his Temple well no what no no
cuz was a side here that's the side I'm
saying it would have gone into his skull
and probably you know jumped around
inside his skull like it may not have
exited the skull it bounc offin it be
it'd be it'd be scrambled eggs
yep it is so crazy how that head turned
to so last minute listen I remember was
the hand of God we listen Jess says that
I know he does um so we we watched this
and at first I was like I went I I think
that clipped his ear and Jess was like
no maybe it's does he have a hair an
earpiece like we you know cuz we didn't
know right away we're still watching it
as it's happening and then when he
stands up and he's got the blood on his
face and starts pumping his fist it was
like oh wow he was hit right he was
definitely hit cuz everybody even even
the commentators were like was he hit
like I don't is this but when he stood
up with the blood it was like holy sh so
what are the convention so so what are
the all the theories on what happened
on the news you've been paying more
attention to this than I have what's
your budd's name Forest yeah forest for
there's a whole group of people on the
internet that are insisting that the
Trump campaign itself hired some sniper
to take a shot at him and just to clip
his ear yeah like like that is for
theatrics like this will push him over
the edge like he's already over the edge
like this isn't not just that any sniper
will tell you listen the wind blows
wrong it can always be off half an inch
to an inch whatever and the fact that
you're going to get him to turn his head
at exactly the same trust me when they
as he was turning his head and that dude
pulled the trigger when that guy pulled
the trigger he did probably still hit
him he's turning his head I mean that's
what that bullet's traveling you know
what I'm saying I I mean there's just
nobody in their right mind that would
hire a sniper to fire you know at their
head it's just Insanity it's amazing how
there's so many people that believe that
is true it's that's Trump derangement
syndrome at its finest then there's the
other ones that no there was a real
sniper that tried to take him out and
the kids of py that's my favorite
because that's very much the um the um
Oswald you know he's a py you know um
Lee Harvey Oswald who was you know
people say like he didn't shoot Kennedy
at all right so yeah he was the Fall Guy
right he's just a Fall Guy and honestly
what a great fall guy like he is perfect
like if you really look at it like is
there a chance like yeah it seems like
this possible there is a definitely a
chance like nobody's ever going to know
for sure why was he perfect because he'd
been to he'd been to the Soviet Union
then they let him back in then they you
know it's almost like he's being moved
around and then the fact that when he
tried to Red defect through Mexico City
right before like a week before right
but then the last minute so he gets a
job at the Texas depos uh Book
Depository and at the last minute they
changed the route of the car to go bu
the Texas Book Depository to be on the
route it wasn't originally on the route
like that to me that's to me the most
compelling part where it's like so we've
got a guy that is the looks like a
perfect assassin you know he's got the
he's he's a you know we can we can blame
it on his views of Communism everything
let's just have the car go right by it
we'll have another sniper shoot him
we'll blame it on him right well and
hopefully he'll just be killed hopefully
the local cops will probably kill him
but they don't he gets he gets grabbed
okay well now he's got to die some other
way the Ruby thing where kind of breaks
down Ruby is probably maybe that was
just an accident like they were hoping
he would never he would be killed by the
local local cops Ruby was definitely not
an accident Ruby was a part of MK Ultra
so when Ruby was in prison he was
getting visited by um you think prior to
this he was set up to kill
him so Ruby was in prison be
um before
was Ruby in prison before or after he
killed Harvey Harvey definitely been in
prison prior I mean he'd been in and out
of prison he was kind of like a he kind
of like was kind of like a a um like a
mob guy he was like a hanger on so in in
uh the book chaos the Charles Manson
book with the CIA by Tom O'neal He talks
about a guy named Jolly West who was a
CIA sort of like psychologist and
chemist I believe he was a chemist but
he was doing tests on people with LSD
um on criminals specifically and there's
documented reports that Tom found that
joli West visited Jack Ruby in prison
multiple times and spent hours with him
and jolly West was very much a part of
MK Ultra the Mind Control experiments
they were trying to uh do in the 60s you
don't you don't know whether that was
prior to that's what I'm trying to find
find out so yeah I'd have to read we'd
have to find the book again or maybe you
could Google it Steve but um I think it
was prior to him killing Lee Harvey
Oswald I think it was very much set up
for him to that I don't think they
wanted him alive and I think Jack Ruby
was probably a part of that plan well I
I we're never going to know we're never
going to know right that's true
um so again okay okay so so there
there's the group of people who think
the [__] that this is I think the least
plausible explanation for it that Trump
somehow hired they the campaign set up a
guy orated to orchestrate a bullet to
fly an inch past his [__] skull
there's no way yeah okay first of all he
didn't need that to win he had already
won the election after that debate with
with Biden there was no shot right so
the second one is the kids of py they're
kind of maybe watching him they know
he's got anti- um you know conservative
or whatever you want you know liberal
leanings he's made a few they haven't
opened his phone yet so you don't know
what that phone but let's say that NSA
has been tracking his phone and they
pick somebody and they say this this
kid's 20 years old he's a shooter like
we know all this by watching his phone
he's a shooter he's extremely
radicalized he's um he's donated to the
whatever to the um uh Democratic uh that
Democratic packed I mean what 15 bucks
not like he's a huge supporter but he's
also 20 so you know he's um uh he's made
you know all of these post or who knows
what he's made you don't we don't really
know yet because they haven't gotten the
phone but let's say the NSA they haven't
gotten the phone no well last I heard
that the FBI is trying to crack it
trying to get into it it's not that easy
if it's got a passcode so it seems weird
that they wouldn't be they they would
I'm sure they'll get into it especially
since they had that Apple thing where
they cracked Apple yeah like but anyway
let's they said they hadn't maybe they
have and they're still reading it who
knows anyway so let's say the NSA
already knew they've got 50 different
people that could be that could be um
homegrown kind of Assassins and this kid
is one of them and he's a shooter and
he's kind of a a loner and they say hey
you know what if we could get this kid
to the rally and maybe somebody stops by
and says hey let's let's radicalize help
radicalize him get him to the rally put
some plant some bom you know bomb
material into his car which they found
um and you know we'll get him on the
roof but we'll have another sniper shoot
at Trump and Trump just happens to turn
his head and it misses who knows so you
know that's the second one is he's a py
and they and this is the maybe some who
knows whether it's the Biden admin
ministration or what these people well I
mean he's not just the py he's also
clearly the shooter right no he's
clearly going to shoot right but Oswald
was probably going to shoot but can we
rely on him to kill him let's get
another person we know can kill him so
let's say that happen so that's I'm
sorry that's another kind of a scenario
where there's another sniper but the
kid's really the Fall Guy mhm okay
that's another one so those are the
two Oddball scenarios the true scenario
is the kids probably radicalize his
father saying he knows nothing about it
right kid kind of radicalizes himself
figures out how to get to the um you
know get to the rally figures a way out
on the rally he had obviously had lots
of of different plans cuz he he did yeah
because he also had um bom material in
his car so it's like maybe he thought
hey can I get on the roof I probably
can't even get on the roof and he
actually you know but if I don't get on
the Rock Roof then here's what I'm going
to do I have this bom material in my car
I'm going to throw it in the crowd or
I'm going to throw it under Trump's you
know SUV or I'm going to who knows what
he's thinking but he obviously had
alternate plans but what happened is he
got out there he said I can get on the
roof he gets on the roof he does the
army crawl you know up the the the back
of the roof the Secret Service agents
see him they call it in other people
Spectators calling in there's a guy up
there with a rifle there's a guy
crawling on the roof MH the secret
service agent is told not to take the
shot to allow them to check it out
first they send in the police police
officer climbs up the ladder approaches
him says hey what's going on the kid
turns around so Kooks turns around with
his rifle points it at him the guy gets
freaked out jumps backwards and actually
falls off the roof the cop the cop does
so he falls off the roof Kooks
immediately turns around gets into
position and starts f firing at Trump
very quickly and so the secret service
agent that had been told not to fire
starts takes him out you know he'd been
told to wait we're checking it out so
and so he goes ahead and takes him out
he heard the bullets flying he heard the
bullets flying so he says [__] that this
kid you know it's it's over he shoots
him from what I understand is the sniper
that we all see in that image on the
roof or the video on the roof where
there's two of them right that are
basically like kind of parallel to Trump
but facing the kid right is that they
had scoped in on that guy five minutes
prior yeah yeah I heard three minutes
but yeah I heard it so I heard it was
five minutes from a guy that uh I heard
that actually talked to him okay uh I
can't I don't think I can say who it was
yet um but a significant amount of time
is five minutes and then he radioed his
superiors telling them about that and
they said Stand Down do not take the
shot or whatever but that's because most
likely because they had said hey let's
get somebody up on that roof to see
what's going on and that's why they send
the police up there so the local cops
sheriffs right they go and they find the
ladder and they climb up there okay but
the snip the scope on that sniper can
see the boogers in that guy's nose you
AG you you are telling me that those
snipers can't tell that he's got a rifle
in his hands I agree but they called it
in like to you know keep in mind too you
don't know that he actually had his the
sniper rifle on Trump at that time at
that time he made have just been army
man crawling slowly up the roof and they
see a guy crawling maybe he's sliding
the gun they don't know if he's got a
gun like you don't really know what he
called in and then he calls it in and
they say okay wait a minute we're send
somebody over there like you is he you
don't know whether he said well I don't
know that he's immediate he's an
immediate threat at that moment he may
not have known that now once the officer
Falls and the kid turns around and
immediately takes aim as soon as he sees
that it's like holy [__] the kid starts
firing which luckily he was he was
obviously anxiety he's panicked he just
starts firing and luckily he doesn't get
a good shot right I with the scope and
that and only you're only 100 you're 130
yards away you're going to hit him Steve
can you play the video that basically
does the countdown of the people
screaming at the guy that's climbing
[Music]
up they atan maybe the pacif yeah
someone's on top of the roof look there
he is right
there right there you see him he laying
down see him yeah he's laying
down see like they don't really
know what's happening see there's a cop
down
there yeah
look we have millions and millions
people country they're talking to the
officer that is insan
on the
roof in recorded history with the best
Border in fact if they it showed the cop
walking along the side of that building
looking up at the guy love so much you
don't mind if I go off telepromter do
you
this damn boring I try to explain that
oh there wow you guys are doing it
they're getting better with time my guys
take a look at that sh take a look at
the arrow in the bottom see the Big R
red arrow right when I left office that
was the Lowe the guy was spotted right
they've sent the cop has probably
climbed up he's climbing up right now
right take a look at that so that arrow
is the lowest am immigration ever
history into our country you know the
starts climbing up the ladder yeah and
then the worst president in the history
of our country took over and look what
happened to our
country now what's this what's going on
here I think they're
walking now look right here why are
these guys shooting people all from
behind
Trump now they have radio look at the
snipers you pause it okay now he yeah he
just
shot so right before the bullets came
the Secret Service were basically like
shooting people out from behind Trump
you see them like rushing people out
photographers
there's a guy
sprinting
[Music]
know all right hope he's tur
[Applause]
the bullets just could you imagine so it
was two minutes right since they since
yeah
well that's good they said they said the
sniper had him in his sights for 3
minutes so whatever three two to three
minutes so but keep in mind that time
period there at some point
supposedly Somebody went up on the roof
a police officer or a sheriff's deputy
whatever actually went up on the roof
and the kid turned around frightened him
and he fell I heard that from I'm only
saying that cuz I heard that from two
different um news organizations both of
them said the same thing like no they
actually came up on the roof but as soon
as he did it the kid Steve have you sold
those little UFO things yet no sales are
just too daunting for me that's why
we're sponsored by Shopify man with
Shopify it doesn't matter how small you
are or what you sell they help you sell
it everywhere across the globe from
their all-in-one online platform to
their inperson Point of Sales system
turn browsers into buyers with the
internet's best converting checkout
platform at 30% better on average
compared to other platforms and sell way
more with considerably less effort with
Shopify magic your AI powered Allstar as
I've mentioned before we use Shopify for
our website that we use for the podcast
to sell our merch it's easy it's
userfriendly anyone can set it up it
takes like 10 minutes to set up to
connect your domain name to it you can
set up discount codes you can upload
variants of different merch it's just
it's unbelievably easy for for anyone
there's no comparison Shopify hands down
wins wow shopify's award-winning help
Powers 10% of all e-commerce in the US
Steve you're going to find it to be a
breeze with Shopify so if you guys want
to check out Shopify and help support
the show you can sign up now for a $1
per month trial at shopify.com
Danny Jones that's all lowercase
shopify.com SL d n j NES to grow your
business no matter what state you're at
again that's shopify.com Danny Jones
it's linked below now back to the show
he obviously panicked and started firing
he's like I got to fire now these guys
are they know I'm up here this guy just
fell I got a fire right and so he just
so my question is if the snipers knew
that the kid was up there 5 minutes with
they five minutes prior to the shooting
and they're rading radioing into their
superiors telling him about it and
they're saying don't fire on him right
why not fire on him for five minutes are
they not focusing on him for that entire
5 minutes are they just like chilling I
think they are oh oh no I'm sure they've
got them in his sights right right okay
I would take them out of my sight so the
second he pulls the barrel of his gun up
they're seeing that right right so there
was obviously quite a bit of delay to
when he pulls his Barrel up looks
through the scope finds Trump and starts
popping off there was a probably what
how long do you think that would take 10
seconds yeah I was going to say 5 10
seconds seems like a long time seems
like a long time and then if you and
then go down to where Trump was the
secret service dog piled him pretty much
immediately pretty quick like two or
three seconds it took them the dog pil
him then they then he stood up after I
don't know how long that was but he
stood up and then the guy's like six3 he
stood up and he's Tower overing these
guys towering over these guys and the
like a couple of them one guy the guy
who looks like Andrew Schultz he's like
holding his hand above his head another
guy's like holding his hand over here
like and Trump like he barges through
six of them to do his like fight fight
fight thing and and if there are if this
is like a JFK scenario where there's
multiple Shooters like like a triangular
hit team right Trump's [__]
done wide open his head was wide open
they let him stand up and like CU he
said hold on hold on hold on and he got
out and they didn't know if there was
another shooter right maybe they got in
something in their ear there you could
hear like the radio they're saying like
what do we do now what saying shoot her
down her down that's probably why they
stood him up and said let's go and they
don't know they didn't know if there was
another shooter or not so if there was
another shooter he'd be he'd be gone
gone but then again Trump's he's too big
to carry it's like they need his help to
get off the stage it's not like they're
going to pick him up and start still
they're the [__] secret service and
there's like seven six or seven of them
right and then there was the one Secret
Service lady you see her but hiding
behind everybody she was like cowering
down behind everybody like hiding yeah
well you know diversity higher yeah um I
mean first of all if I'm 6' three I
you're stupid if I'm 6' 3 you don't get
to be 5 foot2 and and and protect me
like I feel like that's a lot of me
that's still available and these are
these are the main parts that people
shoot at like I'm going to need a taller
Broad in right she's going to have to be
at least six foot with heels I can I'll
take her with heels you know platform
shoes something can't get a 5 fo one 5
foot2 chick no my for me yeah that'd be
fine but no yeah and it's easy you know
like I said you know we're sitting here
in air conditioning with our microphones
talking about what they did wrong of
course talking I'm not saying I know
anything I was talking to Rick pra who's
a legendary um CIA paramilitary guy who
um he was a counterterrorism special
forces clandestine operation specialist
for the CIA was in Nicaragua in Costa
Rica like in the 80s during Iran
Contra he's been in a lot of these
situations not like but he he he wasn't
a the Secret Service but he actually
trained with Secret Service in like the
80s and the 90s trained with those guys
and he knows a lot of them and I he was
like his point was that like yeah you
plan for this stuff a lot but he goes in
every single situation like this whether
it be in combat in war in Black Ops or
in a trump rally he goes after the F the
first bullet
flies after the first bullet flies you
can be
as prepared as humanly possible but
after that first bullet flies your plan
goes out the window right it's the Mike
Tyson Everybody's Got A Plan until they
get punched the face exactly everybody's
got yes exactly man he said everything
goes out the window once the first
bullet flies I think everybody's
screaming about the secret service agent
too I I think that also look you know
they have like an action plan right like
they got it all laid out they know where
everybody is they know everything but if
you've been with the Secret Service mhm
and you're dealing with the local
sheriffs deputies and you know cops or
police stations and everything like
these people don't work well together
you know local sheriffs and and police
don't like the Secret Service the Secret
Service think that they're you know
morons and the truth is is that when you
lay it all out and you look at all and
the first of all and the rallies are
happening one after another after
another can imagine how quickly they
have to they're constantly seeing
different plans and so that sniper on
the roof looking at this guy you and I
can say you saw him you saw he had a
rifle you should have shot him one you
don't know how long he knew he had a
rifle it may have only been for a few
seconds he's being told stand down we
got somebody up there we got somebody
going up there oh okay so in your mind
you're kind of thinking they've got it
handled MH and the other problem is is
that during this period of time what if
he sees him and shoots him and finds out
oh my gosh we didn't have those
buildings we didn't have enough Secret
Service snipers to have those buildings
covered and we agreed to let the local
SWAT team station a guy on the roof and
that was the local SWAT team guy he
wasn't a part of our action plan oh my
God you just killed you just killed a
SWAT team member he's been a police
officer for 25 years right and then
you're like I and then they're saying we
told you to stand down do you see what
I'm saying like I get it I I mean
everybody's screaming you should have
known you I get it but you don't know
everything that's happening in this
guy's head he's being told no no no no
and he may be thinking yeah I think I
know where everybody is but what if I
don't and I'm being told to stand down
now look let's face it once the kid St
got up and started firing he shot him
does it take him 3 seconds to make sure
he's going to shoot the right K hit the
kid maybe that's what took four to five
or six seconds maybe it took him 3
seconds to realize oh my God got a
perfect shot active fire and another
three or four seconds to get a perfect
shot and boom takes him out yeah Lot F
than I'm going to take if you think
about it I mean I've never shot a sniper
rifle but I imagine like look if you you
would you would want him to take the
shot quicker but if he took the shot
quick and missed oh yeah imagine the
time it would take to reload it yeah
then there it would be way you know that
would be way worse for sure listen you
know it's obviously that that but there
was two snipers yeah possi did you see
how they were also kind of like looking
at the scope kind of checking like what
like he like jumped back and like
grabbed it and the tripod kind of fell
back yeah he they're both like what
obviously there was action happening
boring [__] job in the world it's
like being a any any a law enforcement
sitting on a roof for 4 hours it's tons
of boredom with 2 minutes of complete
[__] adrenaline I how many hours has
this [__] guy spent on roofs looking
through a scope and nothing has happened
yeah right imagine how many snipers
spend their whole lives and never fire
at a real person you
know but I mean I I I you know it's it's
so easy to double to to you know what do
you call it um Monday Morning
Quarterback him yeah
yeah here's the real problem is why was
no one on the roof to begin with and it
was so close like like you couldn't put
a sheriff's deputy sitting up there on a
you couldn't give him a fold up chair
some fat Sheriff Deputy couldn't have
sat up there like well they didn't I
mean they they should have but they had
a guy they had a Sheriff Deputy walking
around climbing up the ladder they don't
have a radio they don't have a radio
they're not on the same channel as these
guys like they can't go [__] [__] uh
what's your 20 we got aing kid with a
AR15 on the roof what about the 30
clicks to the right what about the guy
that's a part of that committee that was
that was in Congress that was trying to
pull his D yeah they were trying to pull
secret uh his secret service detail like
what are you doing bro like you know
like like here you know whether you like
Biden or Trump it's like the people that
and this is tons of people on on Tik Tok
like I'm amazed my my videos will get
taken down on Tik Tok if I say the word
gun or somebody says V if somebody says
something even slightly with telling a
story about a guy who pulled a gun or
telling a story about a guy who's
selling drugs they get oh you know uh um
Community violation this is that but you
got people on there right now saying
that too bad the guy missed he should
have been a better shot it's too bad oh
my God he almost got rid of this guy
Trump and and it's like the thing is
when people say that at least they're
consistent right they're calling him
Hitler and they hope at least they're
being honest they've been calling him
Hitler this whole time and now they're
basically saying that they were they're
pissed off you didn't die at least
they're consistent there's also a group
that's saying he's Hitler he's Hitler
he's Hitler oh my our thoughts and
prayers are with Trump the same here's
the thing the same people that are
saying that he's a threat to democracy
want to take
out democracy like this is how Dem we're
voting this is one party this is the
other that's democracy you're you're
want you want them to take out one of
the two parties by say he's a threat to
democracy let's take him out like are
you [__] insane do you know how
insane that sounds like the pract you
know our our country is built on on
voting like just vote like figure it out
I get it do I think Trump should have
you know like you know what the um what
do I think oh him denying that he lost
the election bro you lost the election
you know what I'm saying like you lost I
get it there's there's this there's that
there's all kinds of issues there's some
extra ballots here these weren't counted
I understand but in the
end it's over like quit denying quit
that just say look I lost and and we're
but I'm going to get it next time that's
fine you know I don't think it was fair
whatever I lost you got that but to to
sit here and say that I'm going to take
out the other party like that's just
Insanity like what kind of a person are
you that like I me might not like Biden
but I don't want to the guy to die I
don't want to take him out the kid was a
[__]
20-year-old whose brain was not fully
developed yet and is probably on a junk
load of sris riddlin rid yeah maybe
riddlin anti-depressant every every
school shooter in history had a laundry
list of uh prescription
pharmaceutical prescriptions what about
his dad like his dad hasn't I don't know
anything about his dad oh his dad's just
saying like he's not he's like I have no
idea why he would have done this like I
don't I didn't see any signs that this
was an issue none that's what his
father's saying uh the other thing is
then there were people in the there were
people in the comments who were saying
cuz he's he is a registered uh
Republican the kid is yeah apparently
that's what a lot of antifa people did
and then they're saying
he um but there's also people saying
yeah he voted and he voted for Trump
last time well he couldn't have voted
for Trump last night he would have been
17 years old yeah he would have been
exactly 16 years old but you see what
I'm saying like it makes no sense people
make these rash they say these things
immediately and then I had another guy I
watched another couple of there's a
couple of these where they're like he's
a registered Republican he voted for
Trump the first time but he's so he's
been he's now been so disenfranchised
with all of Trump's lies he de to do the
right thing and get rid of trump it's
like he didn't vote for Trump right you
know like everything you're saying is
ridiculous like you're just making up
stuff mhm so anyway well what are what
those are the conspiracies that I've
heard what what what is your what are
your have you heard anything what are
your thoughts the one that I heard today
from a friend of mine who is I won't say
his name but he was in the CIA and he's
not I don't think he wanted this to be
public but this was just what he told me
in privacy um and confidence over the
phone and I haven't heard this anywhere
else is he believes that this guy was
not acting alone he believes that he was
coerced into doing this and subverted
into doing this by an intelligence
agency is not the CIA right well that'd
be the py thing right he thinks that
this guy was coerced by a foreign
Intelligence Agency of another
country sorry yeah I had not heard that
okay Nei neither had I until this
morning when I talked to my buddy no um
and he said that the one intelligence
agency who is the best at doing this
kind of [__] taking un mentally unstable
people like this and getting them to
commit terrorist crimes mad Iran oh no
not mad mad just gave Trump like two a
hundred million I don't know I threw one
out there
M's the one that's protecting this guy
oh yeah yeah they well they love love
they love Trump oh yeah what he he what
did he do he he moved the um what did he
do he say he just moved the the the the
embassy the embassy where to Jerusalem
yeah he's he acknowledged yeah the
capital or whatever state um but this
guy said uh the
irgc is the best at pulling off
operations like this well I mean he
failed he wasn't a great shooter but um
this is very you can't account for the
fly typical of what they would do yeah
you can't account for the guy climbing
up on the you know ladder and saying
excuse
me what are you doing cop yeah couldn't
account for that yeah so if it was a
foreign intelligence agency how did they
just get lucky that theing secret
service was so incompetent I wonder what
what how much bomb material he had
like that that I wonder because like
okay let's say he he got out there and
he said okay I can't get on the roof
like there's no way there's too many
cops I'm never going to be able to do it
it oh that was his backup plan right
then he then what was was his backup
plan I'm GNA go get my car when Trump
leaves I'm gonna I'm gonna shoot right
up next to him and I'm going to pull
this lever and boom my car will blow up
and I'll take him out too like it was or
I don't I just don't understand how much
material he had in the car like they
haven't said that they just said it was
bomb making material they had up get the
bomb SC bought it was while making
material whatever I just don't know how
much was his car nearby I don't know
there was another thing where they were
saying about the Secret Service like how
did he get his vehicle parked this close
to um you know to to the rally so in my
opinion they they're alluding to the
fact that it had gotten through security
that it would must have been close for
them to be blaming the Secret Service
like how did they not catch this well
they didn't catch it cuz it was a mile
and a half away like they never saw the
car that's one thing but they the the
stuff that I'm reading makes it sound
like it went through security somehow
well I mean you know maybe had in the
trunk the guard sniffing dogs didn't get
it who knows so I don't really know
where it was
yeah yeah I mean if you look at who has
motive to want Trump gone I
mean just look at the last couple years
I mean why would Iran want him gone like
Biden's the one who's bombing Iran like
yeah well well Iran obviously they don't
have a good relationship with Israel
Saudi Arabia and Israel are kind of
aligned against Iran Iran doesn't like
the three the three-headed dragon that
[__] is our and the three countries that
are our biggest enemies are China Russia
and Iran okay so it would probably be
one of the one of those three right if
it was those are our biggest enemies in
the world North Korea is to an extent
but North Korea is more like a [__]
just like nuisance to us how do you get
to a how do you get to a 20-year-old how
do you turn a 20-year-old I don't know
you see what I'm saying like I'm
assuming that's going to take some time
his father's going to miss him for the
the 30 days it's going to take to brain
to to break this kid down brainwash and
reprogram him stick him back that's what
Alex Alex Jones is saying this has got
MK Ultra written all over it like he was
[__] brainwashed I mean his dad it's
not like you would think when the when
the authori showed up he would say like
he was gone for 990 days just got back a
week ago and said hey Dad I'm going to a
rally yeah
yeah or he has he got back he was gone
for 90 days showed up and said dad can
you order this rifle for me yeah well
that's the thing like who weird who has
motive right to to take out Trump well I
mean look at the [__] United States
they [__] they went after Trump he
beat the impeachments he beat rushia
gate he beat the civil cases he beat the
34 bogus felonies he did what no he
didn't beat that he got he he has been
found guilty he found he was found
guilty of the the felonies but it it put
him in a higher regard to the American
public because we everyone saw through
the [__] so it what it did do is
you're right what it did do is it didn't
destroy his credibility which is what
they were hoping for like if we if we
indict him and we try him and we convict
him it will destroy his credibility not
realizing that absolutely didn't harm
him at all that actually made him more
popular yes ex exactly the whole show
trial the whole show trial basically
showed it was like the strian effect
kind of what's going to be more
interesting is that when the state of
New York appet Court overturns like if
they actually if it actually gets
overturned by the appet court then it's
just one more slap in the face like hey
you tried me you had a little you had a
little banana was it Banana Republic uh
um Kangaroo Court put together and you
guys found me guilty but then when it
got to the appet court they overturned
it and guess what I'm not a felon now so
you guys had a good time calling me a
felon and now I'm not a felon and then
the document case was just thrown they
just threw out the the classified
document case today so that was thrown
out why did they do that well you know I
how crazy is that I think it was
suspended for a while because there were
so there were so many things that the
can you find an article on that Steve
the classified document case being
dropped there were all of these kind of
things that the FBI that had done they
had withheld evidence they had staged um
photographs like there was all these
things that made it look very
staged and as a result they the the
judge had kind of like put it suspended
it for a while like we're going to
suspend it for a while and then he
finally just said you know what I'm
throwing it all out Trump's classified
document case dismissal by judge a
Eileen
Cannon so can you find out why they did
it or if there's like if you can like
find like skim through it or find an
article that explains why they did it it
said ruling on that one St so I think oh
oh I think I I read it earlier but I I
believe it was
because something
about the
prosecutor by the way you see the Alex
Baldwin
thing about his case oh that he they
dropped the charges right they dropped
the charges yeah because they withheld
the evidence about the
bullets no what [__] insane judge
dismissed his classified document case
against Trump uh blah blah blah ruled
that the entire case should be thrown
out because of the appointment of the
special counsel who brought the case
Jack Smith had violated the Constitution
he indicated the plan he indicated
indicated he planned to appeal so he's
going to appeal okay well that's not
going to do anything
right
so yeah it's just crazy that this
happens two days after theying try to
kill
him like they're giving him a straight
shot he I mean he has a straight shot he
is the he's essentially the
president-elect right now it's just can
one can he survive to January 20th
that's the thing right like I I talked
to this guy um and a a guy I interviewed
actually for something else but he um we
were texting back and forth and he was
like you know everybody thinks like CU I
was like oh he's he's walking straight
in the office now and he's like yeah but
you have to understand he's like that's
you're assuming he survives right he
this still this guy's got a lot of of
Highly publicized events between now and
then where he could be taken out like if
it was if they were smart they'd Retreat
and say okay we [__] up we'll try
again you know in four years we'll get
another guy in we'll get somebody in
yeah but or they say hey let's Double
Down we'll just take him out at all
means possible and try and bury the
evidence and get away with it so I was
watching Alex Jones Alex Jones videos
all day oh my God and he's saying that
they're going to go For Broke now that's
that's what I'm saying it's like he they
lean all in they are going to go all in
balls to the wall they're going to kill
this [__] and he also said that
after the after he wins the election he
said don't be surprised if you're going
to see a lot of false flag events
happening like he claims they're going
to run truck bombs into like black
churches and stuff and try to incite
some sort of a race war and blame it on
Trump uh supporters unbel like trying to
Target minority communities and use
those as false Flags to create incite
some sort of a crazy civil race war and
then J you know Julian [__] said it
best on his little live stream he did
yesterday he said that if that bullet
would have hit Trump he said it wouldn't
be a civil war he's like Civil Wars
that's cute you think it's going to be a
civil war he goes that's going to be
like the bullet that took out France
Ferdinand that started World War I right
he goes it's going to be World War
[__] three if that would have killed
Trump you wouldn't be able to go outside
dude you still haven't seen Civil War I
haven't watched Civil War yet no I got
to watch did you ever watch the video
where the kid goes
over um what what how a civil war would
play out today watch the whole thing
wasn't it oh okay I haven't watched I
need I need to watch that but I you told
me about this though yeah he breaks it
down so good he's so like like he's he
could care less like he's like he's just
matter of factly like here's this here's
that here's how many here's how many
National Guard troops are in this state
here's how many you know here's how many
um you know he just breaks it all down
very clearly like this is why they end
up winning here's why who wi who who
ends up he ends up saying that the South
wins because basically what he does is
he it's not even against necessarily you
he assumes if you were to break up the
states exactly the way it was split
during the uh Civil War mhm right
Confederacy and the um um and the union
and he took the same states he said well
the states are match different now
there's a massive difference now because
now there's infrastructure there's all
kinds of things and you have all these
State these National Guards units right
he so you assume that the National
Guards units go with the states so now
Florida has how many different you know
what I'm saying so basically if you
break it the the military apart that way
you're on pretty equal footing the real
problem is is that he's like like look
you don't have to invade California you
know what you do is you just cut them
off from their water source which is
coming from out of state and electrical
which is coming from out of state like
he just start also food they don't make
enough food to feed themselves I mean
yeah they have you know they have um yam
yams and [__] you know almonds and
stuff like that but that's not enough to
feed you like they've got a bunch of
foods that they do produce but not
enough to feed their entire population
so he's like and and the interstates
there's only like three interstates that
basically go that way he's like you just
cut those off it's not hard to stop them
from feeding themselves right the the
Confederate states can feed themselves
so he breaks off same thing with power
line same thing he basically is like you
just you don't even have to attack you
just starve them out and he was like so
if you take that plus battles if the
battles are fought and you base it on
the numbers he starts doing the numbers
too listen you he lays it all out and in
the
end the nor can't doesn't win in a
protracted battle they just don't win
yeah if it if there was a Civil War I
don't think it would be like a Democrat
versus Republican type thing right well
I mean he he's B basing it off of what
if the civil wars fought today that's
what his if if there was a Civil War
fought today who would be the two
fighting parties it would be it would be
obviously like
Republican right-wing Trump or Li even
Libertarians Trump types which is
comical by the way one other thing that
which is comical because during the
Civil War the South was the Democrats
the north were the Republicans so that's
commical because it's actually L right
Lincoln was a republican right so now
it's like Florida is Republican Texas is
Republican like you start adding them up
it swapped during Kennedy yeah Kennedy
was the one who changed that
um so why so so yeah what so Kennedy
when he was running he um
John John Newman John Newman explained
this beautifully to us what happened
during the Kennedy election was his
campaign ran an operation to basically
Market themselves in black churches all
around the country and they got they
they they recruited like a preacher to
go around and basically give these
pamphlets and these flyers out to all
the people in the black churches to try
to win over the black vote um he was
also I think he I think he was talking I
don't know if Kennedy actually met with
um MLK but his brother did right and um
and this was like last minute thing and
it swung the black vote like crazy well
Martin Luther King was a republican so
they went after the the yeah you can
look it up um yeah um it was there was a
word there was a word for it that he
used I forget what he called he called
it was like he was like um you could
probably find a Steve I forget there was
a great word for it because up until um
ly Kennedy lynon me Johnson right up
until that era um the Republicans were
the ones who were pushing through all
the legislation for blacks right so up
until that point and they just they
flip-flopped it yeah they said you know
what this is not going well for us right
it's obviously it's going to happen so
we need to take on this agenda we need
to make this agenda take it away from
the Republicans and make it a democratic
agenda and they did they very
successfully over the next several
presidencies did that you know M which
was super successful what were we
talking about before we talked about JFK
oh we were talking about if a civil war
were fought today yeah yeah yeah but
before that we were talking about oh you
talking about okay yeah you were talking
about during the Civil War you were
saying the South were the were the
Democrats yeah yeah slave owners yeah
they were the slave owners they were
that was clu clu's Clan the the the the
um all the the uh cotton um Farmers the
whole the whole thing was all Democrats
listen Democrats didn't like the
emancipation Pro uh Proclamation
Democrats didn't vote for that that was
all Republican like all of these things
were Republican um agendas but then yeah
you're right Kennedy you know good-look
guy goes in there you like you said
black churches get a bunch of reverence
starts put starts pitching to them civil
rights civil and takes that away from
the Republican party like brilliant bro
you have to admit that's brilliant like
this is their this is one of their
winning this is one of their winning
campaigns let's take that from them
let's make it ours and make them the bad
guys yeah you know um I think it was
after the Civil War there was the
Mexican Revolution I think it was like
in 1910 I believe you know and Mexico
used to basically contain all of Texas
and most of all of New Mexico and lots
of Southern California Mexico was
massive it ate up a lot of the United
like current United States and then
after the Mexican Revolution they did a
deal when was the Mexican Revolution you
I said 1910 you said 19 you find out
when the Mexican Revolution was and then
find out like show like the map of
Mexico before the Mexican Revolution and
um yeah 1910 I got it wow look at that
bro man had no idea I wouldn't have even
said it was it no I would have and then
show us a map of Mexico before the
Mexican Revolution it and so after we
got Texas right it was so big and
obviously Texas like like the whole area
of Texas was slave owners right and
doesn't seem that big they wanted to
divide look at that bro that's not it
that's is that it I need you can't
really tell if you can't see like the
whole map of the US anyway so um they
wanted to cut Texas up into a bunch of
States so they would have more voting
power for slavery and they were like no
no no no no that that's why Texas is so
big they had to make it one big state so
they didn't get more voting power like
more States right so okay so you only
get a few Senators right
exactly so yeah it was all about like
control of slavery did you ever see um
in the line back to ass uh
assassinations did you ever see uh in
the line of fire no with Clint Ewood no
oh my God bro it um so it what what a
great movie I mean what a great Clint
Eastwood movie too and he's probably in
his 60s when this when he when he uh did
this movie He plays a secret service
agent that was a part of JFK's detail
when when uh he gets shot mhm and so
it's like literally it's like 30 40
years later and he's still a secret like
longest he was the youngest secret
service agent at the time longest
running secret service agent and what
happens is they end up going into an
apartment where the land lady comes into
the apartment there's something smoking
whatever she accidentally enters the
apartment and finds this wall filled
with photographs of the current
president and Bull's eyes on his head
and um all these different um schematics
of different uh rallies he's been at
shooting points you know that sort of
thing like oh my gosh like this is
somebody who's planning on killing the
president he goes there to check it out
because she calls the Secret Service
couple days later they come they check
it out Clint's character is the main guy
well while he's there the shooter F or
sees him mhm so the shooter sees him and
realizes who he is and starts
communicating with
him um and so they
know
that uh they know that the that this
assassin is planning on killing the
president and it shows how he ends up
getting himself to a position to kill
the president you know John F Kennedy
said like anybody can kill the president
as long as they're willing to to trade
places as long as they're willing to
Forfeit their life mhm right and this
really if you watch this movie let me
tell you something bro the way the guy
gets close like he basically and granted
there's money involved so what he does
is he I don't know if it's Republican
the president is Republican or Democrat
let's say he's a republican so what
happens
is he ends up oh it's John malovich
right like he's the he's the shooter so
he starts donating so he's got a fake
name fake driver's license fake
everything his company's fake it's got a
history everything and he's continually
donating to the party and So eventually
the Republican party you know whatever
the name chairman or whoever is involved
with the chapter that he's you know
friendly with eventually he says hey
there's there's a rally coming up or a
dinner you know a $10,000 plate dinner
you know they have a they'll pay you pay
$10,000 there's 500 people they raise $5
million and you get a picture with the
president so you're going to be next to
the president at some point so he gets
himself invited mhm to this dinner and
he's built himself a composite gun just
like he makes a Dillinger a a very rude
rudimentary Dillinger right with two
bullets mhm and so it's two bullets he
puts it he has a fake stomach and he now
this is obviously before like the really
good um x-ray machines that swoop around
you and can really check you out right
builds this gun right here wow and he
puts it in the fake stomach and the
bullets he has in a um a rabbit's foot
so when he goes through the metal
detector he puts it in the little tray
Ching you know his keys the rabbit's
foot with the keys a plastic gun no no
not the plastic gun the guns in his
plastic guns in his belly but that can
go through the middle detector right cuz
it's composite with no bullets in it the
bullets are in the rabbit's foot which
he throws in tray you know how used to
be you would throw all your your keys in
the tray mhm so the rabbit foot has the
bullets in it right throws them in the
tray walks through they pat him down no
problem he goes to sit next to you know
close to the president under the table
he puts the the bullets in puts the gun
together and then as the president comes
along and shaking people's hands you get
a picture taken with him he's right next
to the [__] guy with a with a gun
that has two bullets in
it bam and then he can shoot
himself wow I'm not going to ruin I I
mean I'll ruin the movie if it's been 30
years or 20 years nobody's going to see
it go ahead it you know obviously Clint
e would at the last minute runs and
jumps in front of the president takes
the [__] bullet you know yeah the guy
shoots somebody else and gets on the
elevator with plenty his wood and there
a whole thing saves president but the
point is if you watch it you're like man
that seems like it' work like how hard
is it listen I got a buddy uh Donovan
Davis the guy from The Gap that story I
wrote yeah yeah yeah Donovan's got
pictures with George Bush I my old uh
Rudy arut which is a guy uh was one of
my business partners he has photos of
him with where he paid $10,000 I think
he paid like $5,000 to be to go to a
fundraiser for for Bush he's got photos
of him with bush wow you know so it's
not that difficult now granted there's
money involved this guy probably donated
$50 to $100,000 to get and this is 30
years ago maybe it's a couple hundred
th000 to get yourself in the same room
but it's not it's not that if you're
willing to realize like hey once I fire
this like I'm dead they're either going
to kill me or spend the rest of my life
in prison you know most people are just
not willing to do that they're just not
no matter how
politically um polarized they are
they're just like look I just don't want
to die right there's not people crazy
enough right like this kid this this kid
that just did this the other day I mean
he was clearly out of his [__] mind
but crazy enough here's the problem is
if you are crazy enough you're usually
not competent enough that kid just
happened to be crazy and competent yeah
how competent though I mean he knew how
to shoot a gun but he didn't really know
how to shoot a gun he wasn't a good
shooter listen if that cop hadn't been
up there if that had gone down a little
bit different he may have Ked actually I
think the sniper probably would have
killed him but that could have gone he
fired eight shots there going right by
Trump right that one hit him I'm
thinking that's maybe not 100% confident
was pretty close yeah it more confident
than I want my assin pretty [__]
close you know I've been thinking the
biggest the biggest
thing that I can't get over here is like
everybody I would say what percentage I
mean I mean there's what percentage of
people think that this guy was a lone
nut versus this was the CIA I feel like
that's the two main camps that that
areas of belief here with this whole
situation I think a majority of them
believe that it was the CIA or the Deep
State trying to take out Trump because
there's so much stuff that's happened in
the last few years with the with the
show trial in New York with 34
felonies uh you know now this the uh
gate all this stuff look who has a
motive the the United States apparatus
whoever's running this thing in the
shadows is the one I believe that has
the most motive whether that's this is
true or not I don't know but it seems
like that's what the consensus is of
most people on the internet that I've
seen you know what's really like what
did Trump do last time that was so bad
he had four years if he was going to do
something insane he would have done it
right and plus just checks and balances
a president doesn't have that much power
what did John F Kennedy say a month
before he was killed he said he was
going to remove 100,000 troops out of
Vietnam every month for four months so
400,000 troops out of Vietnam that was a
military coup The Joint Chiefs of Staff
did not want that to happen they had a
crazy nuclear war plan to Nuke China and
Russia Kennedy and his brother wanted
nothing to do with it and he said you
guys I'm pulling out all the troops a
month later he's dead what did Trump say
Trump said I am going to stop the
funding to Ukraine for this war against
Russia and I'm going to end this
war right then they [__] then a [__]
bullet flies and half inch away from his
[__] temple eight of them I mean it's
it's really you got to have there's got
to be I mean and they they killed that
poor guy in the crowd everybody forgets
about that guy I know the pooring guy
that's the firefighter no less trying to
protect his daughter was there his wife
was there and there's still people that
want to say that it was fake like yeah
get the [__] out of here so this is my
my biggest problem with this is
like it makes sense until the bullet
misses him because if it really was the
CIA Trump would be dead well maybe it's
just a fluke turned his head they would
have had a backup plan they would have
had multiple Shooters you would I mean
I'm sureid find it hard to believe that
if it was the military or a US agency
that they would have missed well keep in
mind too maybe the first thing is let's
send in this kid maybe he's competent
enough to pull it off maybe the second
one is okay he he's human right yeah he
wasn't competent enough but don't worry
there's some more rallies coming up yeah
or yeah you know what I'm saying like
hey don't worry he'll be out in the open
again we'll get him next time right we
have to you know clearly like what we
need is some shorter Secret Service
agents can we get 5' one godam female
agents Jesus Christ
dude the fact that he has the GU balls
to keep doing this stuff he went golfing
the next [__] day I know did you see
that he did like a there was a report
from the cart boy who's like he goes I
watched him do a 20ft putt with a twoot
break he sunk the goddamn Putt and said
the difference between me and that
shooter is I don't
miss what a Savage dude I mean Jesus
Christ you can't you can't me make this
[__] up you can't make this [__] up you
can't write you can't write a better
script dude and then with what he said I
mean he he showed so
muching fearlessness and Defiance when
he was going fight fight fight I mean
like anybody else is like give me the
car get me out of here get me out of
here yeah right for sure for sure he was
like nah it is
it is over unless theying find a way to
kill him man and I really hope they
don't I really [__] hope they don't
because it's going to be utter chaos and
I hope you have a passport to another
[__] country if that happens the
insanity that we're having this
conversation I'm the country that I grew
up in like this is insane I don't
remember people getting shot Reagan got
shot but this was a lone nut job you
know and he was also 5et away from his
car yeah this was like and you never saw
him after that bullet went off they they
dog piled him you never saw him after
that well and you talk and they talked
to you know the thing is he was left
alive and and you you knew right away
what the issue was he was in faua with
Jody Foster he'd actually gone to other
to rallies it just happened to realize
oh what Reagan's gonna be here oh I'll
go maybe I'll get a shot at him and took
a shot uh but um but there's there's
never been any
you know XK Ultra what was it called MK
Ultra MK Ultra you know nobody's ever
said anything but this was just a lone
nut job anyways this guy uh Danny Shen's
a lawyer he uh he rep he worked on the
Watergate case and he worked on the
Pentagon papers case he worked on Iran
Contra case guy goes back right he's
been in like all the most famous cases
in the United States and uh he was
explaining to me the whole backstory of
how Kennedy got killed it's [__] wild
he was saying that when Nixon was was
running for president he was running
against Roosevelt and um Roosevelt
dropped out and then Nixon thought he
had a straight shot doing the presidency
right no they never thought he never
thought for a second that Kennedy was
going to beat him and and he was winning
in the poll Kennedy was losing in the
polls until they did the until they did
the thing with the blacks yeah no no I
was I was saying the the um they did the
debate and Nixon did because Nixon was
sweating he looked so he did so badly in
the debate eight oh that was it yeah
well he starts sweating like he's he
keeps having to wipe it then Kennedy
even though he maybe just held his own
yeah but but Nixon looked so bad he's
wiping his head he because it was super
hot but he's also nervous right
exasperated yeah Kennedy's a good-look
young guy well spoken like all like you
know you know what Nixon look like he
looks like a teror I mean and they go
through the bait and Kennedy just came
off much much more smooth right so Nixon
was the head of this this thing called
the 5412 committee which was part of the
uh National Intelligence and it was
basically he was like a part of this
committee the 5412 committee that was
part of covert Ops for the CIA and after
Roosevelt dropped or not Roosevelt after
um Rockefeller dropped out everyone
thought Nixon was going to be the next
president okay so Nixon wanted Castro
whacked for some reason he thought that
if he could set up an assassination on
Castro to line up with his presidency
would be great so what he did was he
contacted Howard
Hughes the airplane guy I know who right
uses yeah yeah and um Howard Hughes had
this huge connection to intelligence I
mean he was part of like recovering the
glomar Explorer the Russian submarine
all this crazy [__] the spy plane yeah
he did a ton of he had a ton of patents
yes so Howard Hughes went to these two
mob guys who I forget their names who
who were in Vegas and they were like he
Howard Hughes thought he could get these
mob guys to take out Castro or set up a
team to kill Castro the mob guys they go
to Chicago meet with the other head I
forget the other mob guy was in Chicago
they're meeting and they're saying well
this is Santo traficante territory Cuba
right S traficante I think at that time
he was in Tampa but he was like the boss
of like that area and they meet with
Santos traficante in the fountain blue
Hotel in
Miami and Santos traic is like H well
you know I got to make sure that this is
really in order they're like they're
like the President Nixon who's about to
be the president is is wants this done
can you get this done for us he's like
well if you can prove that he really you
know right made this order and this is
not you guys just doing this so they got
a guy for the a CIA employee to come
down to represented Nixon to give
traficante the green light so traficante
recruits these guys from this uh CIA
operation Operation 40 who were these
anti-castro Cubans who were conducting
sabotage inside
Cuba um when Castro and Chay and Raul
were down there you know doing their
thing and these operation 40
guys um they picked a few of them I
think it was 10 or 15 of them and they
brought them to this Ranch called Waka
Ranch and they were and another Ranch
that was in South Florida like near the
Everglades and they were training these
guys in what were called triangular fire
teams so they would set up in a
triangular formation of three Shooters
to take out a moving Target and this was
all in plans to kill
Castro after training these guys they
obviously they went they you know you
know the stories they went down to Cuba
to try to assassinate Castro it they
went twice it was a failed attempt both
times to kill
Castro and then later
on um it was this same Cubans so those
Cubans were the ones that they tried to
use to kill Kenny
so when kenned when they wanted to
assassinate Kennedy they figured out
they found out like the best shooters
that we know that hated Kennedy because
of all the [__] that Kennedy did after
the Bay of Pigs and all that stuff were
these anti-castro Cubans they were great
Shooters they knew they could cover it
up and theying hated Kennedy so he was
saying those were the uh the guys who
actually pulled the trigger in D Plaza
that killed Kennedy later on there's
Watergate the guys that were caught in
Watergate was Bernard Barker was one of
them he was one of the anti-castro
Cubans now the way they were funding
these guys at this Ranch this Waka Ranch
in Mexico during the Triangular fire
team training was through a bank called
the Bano
International and this
bank is complicated but they were
skimming money off the mob casinos
sending it to Meer Lansky's Bank in
Miami and they were wiring it from Myer
Lansky's Bank to the bank bank
International in Mexico to pay these CIA
mercenaries to train them how to kill
Castro
um which were eventually the same guys
they used to kill the President right so
fast forward to
Watergate one of the guys that were was
in the hotel that got caught had a bank
note in his pocket had a a bill right
they traced the bill back to that same
bank now there was an FBI guy who was
trying to investigate that dollar that
that uh bank note find out where it came
from somehow um the guy in Nixon sta in
the White House finds out about this
investigation calls up Richard Helms in
the CIA and another guy in the FBI says
you need to meet with this guy uh uh
Mark Mark fent or Mark something I
forget his name they said you need to
you need to stop this FBI investigation
into that bank account because if you
find out what was going on with those
Cubans and why we were training them
down in Mexico you're going to peel off
a scab and you're going to unleash a
genie that we can't put back in the
bottle because they knew if they
investigate that bank they would find
out that those were the guys that they
used to kill Kennedy and Nixon knew if
they found out that those Cubans were
the ones that did Kill Kennedy they
would be able to trace those Cubans back
to Nixon and they would think Nixon was
the one who tried to kill Kennedy which
he wasn't he would use those guys to
kill Castro so he stepped down to stop
the investigation so no there was a
whole another thing with the
investigation there there was um I
forget the guy's name the other FBI guy
there was a bunch of [__] involved with
Watergate but basically the the idea
behind Watergate the reason that this is
what Danny Sheen says the reason for
Watergate was they he wanted those guys
to break in because they were going all
of um Howard Hughes who was Nixon's
biggest financial backer biggest Lobby
is for Nixon all of his if they found
out all of his stuff that was in that
hotel they would find out about the
shooters so they didn't Nixon didn't
want any connection to him hiring those
assassins to kill Castro because if they
found out about that they would find out
that the same guys killed Kennedy and
they would make the connection from
Nixon to Kennedy yeah I understand they
would they would assume that which it
wasn't true but that was the reason for
Watergate according to Danny shien and
crazy complicated right but it's it's an
insane story
okay I mean I thought Watergate they
were just breaking into the uh
Democratic Pary uh headquarters just to
try and plant bugs yeah that's that's
the that's the story right but according
to Danny it was way bigger way deeper
than that it was because they didn't
want to find out about who really killed
the president and Danny claims that
there's still Cubans that are alive
today anti-castro guys who were part of
that CIA operation 40 who actually were
responsible for Killing Kennedy so what
happened with Nixon anyway first he ran
against he ran against um johnf Kennedy
he lost then Kennedy got killed and LBJ
took LJ stepped in stepped in then LBJ
was he re eled and I don't think so or
did he lose against did he lose against
cuz then cuz then Nixon runs again mhm
and wins and wins that's when Watergate
happens then he yeah well once he once
he won yeah cuz he was about to start
running again so he's going to he wants
some inside information on I thought
that's what that's the historic version
is he wanted inside information yeah
there's a lot of different theories on
on Watergate but this was like the
wildest one that I've ever heard um and
Danny shean was a part of that whole
investigation so he would know he he
Danny actually interviewed that mob guy
traficante in Miami and traa con told
him that that's why those guys were
breaking
in what next straight from theing
horse's mouth it doesn't get any crazier
than that dude another thing about
Trump
is ever since that debate with Biden I
mean that was a [__] brutal moment
too that was like I think I think that
was the moment after that in that debate
where he goes I don't know what he the
he just said I don't think he knows
either that that was like okay this is
done after that he was actually way more
reserved than I thought he was he that's
what I'm saying he he's been super
reserved super magnanimous yeah since
that election right he hasn't been
typical Trump I think during his first
during the first um you know
presidential run or whatever you want to
call it um I think he learned a lot like
I think he you know what I'm saying I
think he learned like like there you
just can't say some stuff you know what
I'm saying you not that he's learned a
ton but he's definitely he's tapered
back the rhetoric not a huge amount but
let's say 20% 30% like he could have
really been brutal to Biden but he
wasn't but he doesn't have to be anymore
like like it's like let's listen I
remember one time he doesn't one time I
was evicting this guy and he was a he
was a former um uh Vietnam vet M we had
bought a bunch of we bought like 20 my
my wife at the time we bought like 20
units and so there's this guy who's
literally got a water hose hooked up and
then when we're trying to show the
apartments MH he's hosing people down
and when the other tenants would come
around he'd hose them down like he was
just he was just a huge nuisance right
and he was crazy and so we just started
evicting him now he pay his rent
his rent was nothing either we wanted to
raise the rent by two or 300 bucks he'd
been there he' just been pain in the ass
so we when we finally get to and he did
everything to stop it he hired an
attorney they tried we went to mediation
and every you know he's just lunatic
keep going he was a lunatic what ends up
happening is he um he ends up when we
finally get to court because the problem
was he's paying his rent into the court
you know what I'm saying like what a
pain in the ass this guy because we're
not we're not evicting him for we're not
evicting him because he's um not paying
he's paying that's the worst of it he is
paying but he's such a nuisance we want
him gone right he doesn't have a lease
anymore his lease is expired he just
wouldn't leave but he keeps paying so
anyway we're trying we're trying to
evict them we end up getting into court
and when we got into court the judge
comes up and he's like okay listen
there's this they filed the three-day
notice they filed the you know the the
10day notice they did this they did this
you've been served like well what is
going on here you let's say the guy's
name is like Mr Johnson Mr Johnson no wa
he says okay what's going on he looks at
me he goes Mr Cox he said he said what
what's going on here like I'm gon to let
you talk first and I went you know your
honor I said I think you'll have a
better understanding if you let Mr
Johnson explain and he okay he's like
whatever jackass like he's like all
right Mr uh Mr Johnson why don't you go
ahead and explain and he's like your
honor I'm a Vietnam vet and these
criminals they're all over the place and
I have to I use my hose so that I don't
shoot them and and and and they're
everywhere and the and he just start he
Rants and Raves for like five and as
he's doing it the judge is staring at
him and at some point he looks over at
me and I
go like that and the judge goes okay Mr
Johnson I I think I understand what's
going on here he
said I'm and then he he what was that
it's the alarm for kiraku oh oh and then
we got five minutes and then he goes he
ends up the judge goes I'm going to go
ahead and I'm going to allow the you
know blah blah blah you've got 10 days
to vacate or you'll be you'll be you
know removed blah blah blah and it was
over that was it it's over guy's still
screaming when the judge [__] hauls
ass you he walks out like they have like
a side door judge like bolts out the
side door the guy's still screaming we
just walk away but it's like that's kind
of like how I felt Trump was at the
thing he's like I don't even have to say
anything go ahead and you answer this
question like the more you answer these
questions Biden
the more people understand you can't let
this continue I mean even not even just
during the the debate though but like
even after theing assassination attempt
like he wasn't on Twitter talking all
this [__] like calling out the the
[__] radical you know he he hasn't
been as divisive as he was when he was
first president he's been very very
reserved and even like his statement
afterwards like saying like giving
condolences for the people that were
killed and all this stuff like it's
interesting and like when he talks on
Thursday it's going to be interesting
cuz there there's reports that he
rewrote his script for his speech right
right so I'm wondering if he's going to
take the opportunity to come out and
unite the country and not be I think the
country so overwhelmingly polarized
there's nothing he can say people don't
want they they don't they just don't
want to believe they don't has he over
some more people probably you know I
mean but the people that are dug in
they're they're they're lunatics like
the people that are they're they're just
not there's no reasoning with them he's
a racist he called for this he called
for that like when show me the film when
did he say this when did he say that he
doesn't need the polarizing de decisive
divisive messaging anymore though he
doesn't need that it's done he he's
already won my point is can what I'm
saying is that those people that have
already decided to vote for bid their
voting for him no matter what Trump says
right it doesn't matter for sure for
sure if Trump if Biden came out and
started saying just horrific things they
wouldn't change their vote no nothing
would change it no so there's nothing
for him to do the P's got his base it's
more than 50% it's it's going to be a
landslide in the electoral vote and he's
like I've got it I just have to not say
anything overwhelmingly stupid at this
point which I'm sure his handlers that's
an issue you know he's always going to
trying to say something crazy so they're
probably like just stick with what the
teleprompter says that's it it's all you
have to do you walk into the into the
White House what do you think he's going
to do to get rid of the the Ukraine
situation what do I think he's going to
do I you know on day one he's going to
want to try and nip that in the butt I
mean I hope he does I hope I mean I look
I don't know [__] about [__] about how
that works or like who's in charge of
the Ukraine war I know it goes deep in
into like the EU is involved with this
and the the globalists as Alex would say
and um there's a lot of other countries
that are really invested in this War I
don't know how he would pull out of that
I I I I think it might be somewhat
easy
um but there's a lot of there's a lot of
pieces on that chess board to move to
make that happen but um just the threat
of just him saying he's going to do it
has people freaking the [__] out I mean
I think that's all you have to do is
freak Putin out you just have to get
Putin to say okay oh you have just kind
of go in there and say look you keep
what you already have that's it what you
got you got that's it and then or we're
going to send in US troops yeah we push
you out diplomacy man it's just like I
think he I mean that's the one thing
that he did when one of the good things
that he did John what's up man thanks
for coming on and uh and talking to us
on this on this little we're doing this
little podcast just trying to like uh
react to what's been going on with the
whole Trump thing and and how it
happened uh I know you have your show
that you do every day and you guys have
been covering this uh what is your view
on what happened on I think it was
Saturday with Trump and uh everything
that's coming out what is your uh view
on everything you know I think the I
think the easiest explanation is
probably the best explanation at this
early stage and that is that this was a
colossal historic screw up on the part
of the uh Us Secret Service you know let
me add a little detail too I grew up
walking distance from this uh this
location uh the Butler County
fairgrounds and farm show never missed a
year when I was a kid there's nothing to
do in Western Pennsylvania um and so we
would go to the farm and the and the
Farm Show in the fair and it's a big
deal because politicians always come and
they have these events so it's not like
this the first time anybody's ever come
to Butler County you know this is
something that they should have been
used to now getting to the screw up here
you've got a guy that's not just a
presidential candidate Presidential
nominee but he's a former president of
the United States and the only job of
the uh Secret Service is to
protect the candidate that's it and what
they're telling us
today is that they essentially
outsourced uh coverage of these external
buildings to the Butler County
Pennsylvania Sheriff's Department you
know when I first heard that I I I
wanted to laugh because this is
literally not something you would ever
do if you are the the Secret Service and
going back just a little bit you know
there were there were two major uh
assassinations in uh in 1968 of course
um in
1972 George Wallace was uh was shot and
wounded in Laurel Marland he was running
for president on the American party
ticket in
1981 uh Donald uh Donald Trump uh Ronald
Reagan was shot and and grievously
wounded so after each one of these these
shootings there was a top to bottom
review of The Secret Services procedures
this is this is the term that they're
using yesterday and today top to bottom
review so we we've gone from 1981 until
Saturday with no credible attempts
against the life of a candidate so why
now how was a 20-year-old able to climb
to the roof of a building within direct
line of sight of the former president of
the United States stay there for quite
some time be confronted at least twice
that we know of and still get a shot off
that doesn't make any kind of sense to
me at all major major screw up and not
only that but after the Secret Service
agents jumped on top of him and dogpiled
him they let him stand up with shoulder
to head fully exposed around those guys
as he barged through those Secret
Service agents to like show his show his
strength and like pump his fist to his
audience if if there was a second
shooter if this was anything Sim
remotely similar to the JFK setup if it
was a triangular hit team or multiple
shooters or whatever that was a turkey
shot an easy shot for a second shooter
to get off even after that first guy was
neutralized you are exactly right you
are 100% right and let me add something
to that too um I happen to be with my
son my my 20-year-old son when we heard
news of this attempt on uh on Donald
Trump and he said to me you know he said
about four weeks ago I went to a Nascar
event in North Carolina right 50,000
people in this in this whatever it is
track and Donald Trump was the the guest
of honor so they have him stand on this
balcony on top of the uh the the Press
uh area where where the Press has
gathered to overlook the uh the track
he's the only person wearing a red hat
he was standing out there in front of
everybody there was no security to get
in you didn't have to go through any
metal detector or anything and he turned
to his girlfriend my my son did and said
said my God if somebody wanted to kill
Trump he said this would be like fish in
a barrel so apparently this is a this is
a bigger problem than just somebody
screwed up on Saturday this is a problem
with the actual standard operating
procedure of protecting a candidate that
uh that the secret service has
implemented now you you were in CIA for
how many years 15 15 years and you were
overseas in war zone
with working with armed military taking
out people like abuaba capturing him and
I'm I'm sure you've been in situations
similar to this where there has to be
like a perimeter set up or like a like
people that have to be on watch how does
this typically work do you know anything
about like how the perimeters have to be
set up how wide they have to
be yeah actually and I had this
conversation today with a friend of mine
who happens to be a former FBI agent as
well and we were in agreement that you
have to sweep literally every building
you set up a perimeter a perimeter
around or that includes every building
with line of sight uh to the candidate
and you keep sweeping it now if there
are buildings multiple buildings you
have somebody on literally every single
roof just so that something like this
doesn't happen and as long ago as 10
years
we were using drones to supplement uh
the human surveillance uh at places like
bam Airbase you know bam you've got a
prison in the center and then there's a
perimeter around that and then you've
got the living area and you've got the
working area and there's a perimeter
around that then you got guys outside
the fence walking that perimeter but
then you've got you know two three four
drones overhead and somebody inside
monitoring the Drone coverage again this
is a former president of the United
States and there was no drone coverage
like we're supposed to we're supposed to
just accept that the Butler County
Pennsylvania Sheriff's Department was
responsible for this no that's just not
real life and is it possible that the
sheriff's department I mean there's
footage of the guy climbing on the roof
with cops walking around the building
looking at him and then there was
obviously like everyone's aware of the
report of the cop actually climbing up
there and then like falling off after
the guy points his rifle at him is there
any sort of radio frequency between
these cops and the Secret Service like
you would imagine that the cop would be
able just to like turn on his radio
right then and there and say shooter no
in most cases no so what in most cases
because this is just like a not just
even a one day event it's a one hour
event or three-hour event altogether the
the cop would radio back to his dispatch
dispatch would be liasing with secret
service and then the the Secret Service
dispatcher would uh would radio Secret
Service so you're going to lose you know
15 seconds maybe which is plenty of time
to kill somebody but that's how
haphazardly this was this was arranged
and you know it it's easy to fall into
this uh this this rut well you know
nobody's taken a shot at a presidential
candidate since 1981 they're not going
to do it in Butler Pennsylvania let's
just get through this one hour and then
we wrap it all up and we go on to
Milwaukee I guarantee you that's what
these guys were thinking and the sniper
there's reports that the sniper saw the
guy on the roof like five minutes before
he took the shots and they were looking
at him the whole time and then he like
he was radioing his Superior about it
they knew he was there and they said
don't take the shot and I assume I don't
know what it's like to be a guy who sits
on the roof with a sniper for 3 hours I
can't imagine how boring that must be
especially when you're doing it like on
multiple events like throughout you know
whatever the month but like I imagine
there's got to be some sort of fear of
maybe like maybe that guy is like a SWAT
guy I don't know about on that roof I
don't want to take out like an innocent
cop or something like that what what do
you make of of that guy being aware of
the guy being there and not being able
to take the shot and tell there was
eight shots fired well your your
assumption is exactly correct so the can
you imagine you're a sniper for the
Secret Service you go through a 30-year
career and never ever fire the weapon I
[__] imagine to that's that's what we
were saying that's crazy but yeah your
your thought is a good one uh the sniper
has to be thinking is that one of the
cops is that a Pennsylvania state
trooper is it you know the janitor for
that building who wandered onto the roof
to get a better look uh should I shoot
him if I shoot him I'm trained to kill
him so maybe I shouldn't shoot him I
should probably radio in and say hey
there's this guy now as it turned out um
rather than once shots were being fired
rather than radio back to dispatch and
and ask for permission to shoot he just
shot which you know thank God he did
right but um but the system is such that
it's not efficient enough to save a
candidate who's under Fire it's just not
can I ask a question yeah oh yeah I got
uh my friend Matt Cox is here he wants
to ask you a question as well do does he
think that it does he think that it was
just incompetence or does he think that
there's a possibility that
it was done
specifically for a reason like to to
leave open you know a I don't know an
opportunity for someone to take a shot
sure lots and lots of people are talking
about that today and yesterday and my my
gut response is is no or likely likely
no only
because only because an operation like
that would have so many moving parts
that it would be virtually impossible to
carry out and I mentioned this today to
this FBI friend of mine and she saidou
know she's giving this a lot of thought
as well and if they were going to do
that they wouldn't have outsourced it to
a to a 20-year-old you know just some
local Yoko from from Bethal Park
Pennsylvania um and they wouldn't have
done it in front of thousands of people
it's just not the way they would carry
out an operation like that not that they
have in the past right that's not what
I'm saying but in the event that there
was an operation they they would miss
yeah they would they would number one
they would they wouldn't they would if
it was the military or any kind of us
any kind of us organization they Trump
would not be here right now so so that's
right is he so what you're saying is if
it's a py situation where the kid is
just a py at the very least they're
going to have snipers to take them out
to take out Trump you're exactly right
and there there would have to be
secondary and tertiary levels just in
case the kid missed the kid needed to be
taken out right you remember you
remember seeing the video of Lee Harvey
oswal saying I'm just a PSY right before
he was killed you know that's that's
something I I think we're always going
to have to be thinking about in
situations like this
now what do you make of I mean I've
watched I've been watching as well as
everyone probably has been watching I've
been watching hundreds and hundreds of
people's takes on what happened over the
last two days and it seems like an
overwhelming majority of people who have
been looking at this and people talking
heads on YouTube that have been you know
doing a play byplay the consensus is
that it was the United States that was
behind this or the quote deep state was
behind this because their evidence is
like look at the last four years of how
they tried to take out Trump with all
these other things with like you know
there was Russia gate there was the the
trial the show trial in New York then
there was um what else
the the document the document case yeah
there's so many things that they've
tried to do to take him out of the race
and then now you have an assassination
well isn't that convenient right like
that seems to be the overwhelming
consensus and I don't know because I
wasn't alive back when Reagan they tried
to take out Reagan but was was it like
that re wasn't taking nobody tried to
take out Reagan who the who's the guy
that was shot it was reagy yeah Reagan
was shot by John Hy trying to impress
Jody Foster right exactly so when was
shot was that was America talking about
it the way they're talking about it
right now like was America thinking like
oh my God this was America that took him
out or the Deep state or whatever no no
no no the whole country pulled together
Reagan's popularity went into the 90s
the whole country came together right um
it's so different you know you and I you
and I Danny have talked about this in
the past I I've been in Washington for
42 years I came here I moved here the
week after I turned 18 to to go to
college and it is become such an ugly
mean-spirited City it's I'm not able to
compare it to any other place that I've
that I've been in the world uh and so
that's why we have these these rumors
that's why we have you know rational
people like people I respect for example
going on Twitter going on Facebook and
saying it was the Deep State well like I
said there there are so many moving
parts to a conspiracy that if it was the
Deep State they would have gotten him
ages ago they wouldn't have to have you
know trumped up federal and state
charges and and you know found this
20-year-old idiot to climb onto a roof
they would have gotten him they would
have got him somehow yeah I've got a
buddy who's a who's a retired um colonel
in the Army and uh and kind of a
prominent Republican fundraiser now and
he told me over the weekend that he went
to uh he went to Mara Lago about six
months ago for for a a fundraising event
and um he and his wife are they not only
have Concealed Carry Permits but they're
concealed carry instructors and so he
pulls up to Mara Lago and the Secret
Service stops him at the gate and hey
hey folks how are you tonight uh do you
have any weapons in the car and he said
actually we do we've got two weapons in
the trunk but they're both secured the
Secret Service guy says I'm sorry you
can't bring them onto the ground he said
fine he let his wife out drove back to
the hotel locked up his guns in the safe
and then went back to Mara Lago 15 20
minutes later but he said the point is
nobody ever searched the car right and
if if he had said no I don't have any
guns he could have walked right into
that Ballroom fully
armed wow what is the what is the Secret
Service thinking I this is a
systemic problem here it's not just what
happened Saturday it it's through the
entire system of protection that the
Secret Service is supposed to be
implementing right what what how much
credit do you give to the idea that it
could have been a uh a foreign adversary
like China Russia or Iran right well
that's something that the FBI me uh
mentioned right off the bat that it's
something that they have to consider how
how how possible or how probable do you
think something like that would
be unlikely you know when when John
Kennedy was killed uh the Soviets came
to us within minutes uh and at the CIA
you know we keep all these historical
documents you can as a junior analyst
you can just go through them and get an
idea of what it was like back then they
came to us within minutes of Kennedy
being killed and saying we swear to God
it wasn't us we swear it wasn't us the
Chinese did the same thing and then the
Cubans asked the Mexicans to tell us
look it wasn't us right so that that I
mean I mean that's that that's a trigger
for World War II absolutely if you try
to take out a a candidate for president
of the United States yeah not worth the
blowback potential once again you're not
going to use the 20- year old it's the
same thing it's there it's going to be
even if they're going to do it it's
going to be a successful operation
they're not going to leave anything to
chance yeah they're not going to put it
in the hands of a 20-year-old kid so and
it's not going to be from 145 yards
either it's going to be from 500 yards
or 800 yards where have any idea where
it came from if you're going to if
you're going to use a Professional
Sniper to do it first of all he's not
going to use an
AR-15 uh with you know by all it counts
you know 22 or 5.56 or whatever whatever
you know rounds rights he was shooting
if you have a Professional Sniper he's
going to be so far away you can't even
see him and he's not going to
miss yeah it's uh it's crazy man what
what what do you think
what do you think would have happened if
that bullet would have hit him and take
and and taken him out what what do you
think the reaction would have been
there's I heard a take um my buddy
Julian was saying that if if the bullet
would have hit him it would have been
like a France Ferdinand moment the
bullet that took out France feran to
started World War I he said he said he
said Civil War doesn't even do it
justice it would be it would be far
bigger you know I mentioned a few
minutes ago Danny so many of my friends
like a lot of high school friends for
example who still live in the area in
Western Pennsylvania these are people
I've liked and respected all my life we
may not agree on politics but we like
and respect each other we're in each
other's weddings we visit each other you
get the idea um and that's exactly what
they were talking about they would have
armed themselves within moments and they
would have taken to the streets right I
think that's exactly what would have
happened yeah this was as close a call
as we could have had so like I guess the
idea like I I understand what you're
saying if this was an intelligence
operation it would have been successful
it would not have been so
sloppy but like what about the idea that
the kid could have been MK Ultra or like
they like like some sort of foreign
agent could have used him and coerced
him and subverted him into talking him
up and saying oh this might be a good
idea even if it was a failure maybe it
could it could at the very least incite
chaos in the US and disrupt the system a
bit and disrupt the populace you know at
the very best maybe the freaking the
crazy kid gets lucky and hits his shot
but you're saying you're essentially
saying that no that's too sloppy even if
it was just a one kid that they tried to
brainwash or subvert somehow um they
would have had a backup option in place
yeah they would have and you know not
every country uh is is capable of
carrying out an operation like that
especially if if you're talking about MK
Ultra and mind control and hypnosis and
all that stuff you're talking about
three four five countries that are able
to do it Russia China Israel North
Korea that's probably about it right um
well we know it wasn't Israel Israel
just gave him 100 billion or hundred
million dollars right yeah Adon right
yeah exactly right 100 150 million
something like that Israel but yeah it
again the the the blowback potential is
such that you know I mean let's say the
Chinese did this right and and we were
able to develop information confirming
that the Chinese had done it I mean
you're talking about a nuclear exchange
being the next
step if it had been successful and we
Chinese Matt has a
question first off I think it was just a
20-year-old but yeah you know for the
content sake um
assuming it assuming that it was um I
don't know whatever you want to call it
deep state or you know a an attempted
assassination that
failed and you
know do if it was an attempted
assassination that failed in your
opinion do they just take their ball and
go home or do they and and and just say
hey Trump's gonna win it we messed up or
do they try again Ah that's a good
question question very good and I agree
with you I think it was the kid um but
if it were an operation yes you pick up
the ball and you go home let's use as an
example of pigs oh yeah yeah once once
you've blown it that's it it's done it's
over You Had Your Shot it was one shot
it's over um that and then you deal with
a blowback you know that's why you got
to get it right the first time look at
the look at the Bay of Pigs for example
the only reason that the Bay of Pigs
failed was because John Kennedy made a
strategic policy decision not to provide
air cover right so we didn't say all
right everybody let's try it again in
two weeks and this time we use air cover
no we just we took our lumps and went
home and and that's the way that's the
way it
happens okay finally maybe you can
educate us num skulls on who is this guy
who's the new vice president
and and what do you make what do you
make of that can you give us uh some
sort of like educated opinion on on this
guy and what this means yeah this is
actually kind of a bold a bold Choice um
so JD Vance is uh he's he was famous
well before he ever entered politics
he's very young he's 39 years old uh
he's a self-made billionaire uh from a
hedge fund that he created on Wall
Street but this guy grew up in abject
poverty in the Appalachia
area of Southern
Ohio and um he was raised by his
grandmother his mother was a heroin and
meth addict and was never a major part
of his life and so his grandmother
stressed education education education
and he was a smart kid and so he won
scholarships he went to school he ended
up going to Yale and uh then made it big
big on on Wall Street he wrote a book
called hillbilly elegy talking about
coming out of this abject poverty but
not as a
lefty uh he he picked him up himself up
by his bootstraps and he he did it
through hard work not because welfare
paid for this or welfare paid for that
that's what hillbilly elegy was about it
became a quite a popular and successful
movie and then he decided to uh to go
into politics now the interesting thing
to me is that he was an anti-trump
Republican for a long time I saw that he
wrote quite a powerful oped saying that
Donald Trump was an idiot and a monster
and then we learned from Donald Trump Jr
just a week ago that the choice probably
wouldn't be JD Vance because Donald
Senor has um has this visceral dislike
of facial hair and he had mentioned to
family members he couldn't stand the
thought of looking at JD Vance every day
with a beard and
mustache oh my God that's insane guyy
smart he's Rich he's self-made he's a
great campaigner and like I say I think
this was actually a pretty bold Choice
interesting well awesome uh I can't
thank you enough John I appreciate uh
all your Insight and for answering our
questions here today it really it gives
us some credibility here uh for doing
this podcast we don't have any we have
no business talking about this kind of
[__] by
ourselves so thanks again man I really
appreciate it yes sir I love you man and
I'll I'll talk to you very soon bye bye
looking forward to it see you
John I tell you what makes me feel
better is
how how close everything we said was to
what he's kind of saying you know what
I'm saying it was pretty not perfect but
pretty close yeah except for the me
saying like there I they're not going to
take their ball and going home he's like
oh no no take your ball and go home
everyone else is yeah that's what was
saying the opposite he goes they're
going for [__] broke yeah interesting
well but um the stuff we will see yeah
the other stuff was um spoton I thought
we gave some oh wow look at that we can
see ourselves look at you Matt Cox you
look godamn do I really look like that I
need a [__] haircut dude are you
kidding me look when I smile look when I
smile let me see let's see let's see
Matt smile look look at that beautiful
smile look at this is INS oh the crow's
feet mat you need some get in Botox dude
I'm not doing it I don't want to do it
it's embarrassing enough I got the hair
plug look how great your hairline is
though it does look amazing your
hairline looks fantastic dude but oh man
I need to lose some weight oh did I tell
you this oh God if I've been hunching
over my God
Stephen you couldn't say something I'm
getting haircut tomorrow I look terrible
at least if my wife was here she'd be
holding her shoulders back like your
shoulders back um you want to hear
something uh funny yeah is I'm supposed
to be going on on a fresh and fit oh
yeah you told me that tomorrow right no
no no no this is like the 22nd I'm sure
they record I'm sure they record them
and put them out but but like like I've
talked to them or their business their
producer whatever back and forth on the
email and you know and here's the thing
like I'm flying in there and then I'm
flying to Dallas because I have a um uh
like a speaking not speaking thing but I
have like a a sh that I have to do and
then I'm flying back like I'm like boom
boom boom like all I feel like a big
shot you are a big shot my God that's
insane um but uh I still haven't got the
address I mean I'll get the address but
other than that it's confirmed though
it's in Miami right they said it was
confirmed bro like I don't know you know
it's yeah no it's in Miami it's on
Bickle by the way we haven't even talked
about this yet you haven't we haven't
talked about this since you did it you
were you did the longest podcast ever
recorded on Lex fredman's Channel no we
did talk about it didn't we talk about
that that podcast never aired oh you put
it on patreon that's how you get the
patreon people that's right exclusive we
use Matt as a as a
little what a great [__] what a great
day for you man the patreon that was
pretty cool pretty
cool yeah anyways I mean Patron sorry
The Lex fredman thing what is this Trump
shooter was oh yeah dude this is so oh
yeah so Demolition Ranch these guys in
Texas shirt he had the shirt yeah man I
know these guys guys and I was just
talking to him last week and then I saw
I just saw today the dude was wearing a
Demolition Ranch shirt yeah and now this
guy's getting a I don't know if he's
getting a lot of [__] I don't know but I
I mean he said he's been getting a lot
of like media questioning him about it
so what so this is his he made a
statement on um them wearing his shirt
what let's see what he
said horrible wow the audio is terrible
why is it so [__] bad Jesus Christ
hold on Julian tell audience oh jul and
Dory finger on the pulse give us the
update nobody's got more inside info on
the Trump assassination than Julian
[__] Dory he's already done a
100 podcasts on this thing he's been up
for three days straight just got off a
live stream with Jim diorio special
agent the most underrated podcaster on
YouTube yes Julian what's happening are
we on air we're on air baby we're on air
holy [__] we're on air we're doing it
live what's happening dude how what's
Jimmy D say about this Jimmy D just
dropped balls of fiery Flames for two
hours on a podcast while I was in
production hell so I'm gonna listen to
it back and see what he said but it
sounded really smart yeah we were
watching it he has he lost weight oh
yeah he's lost a lot of weight dude he
looks way thinner he looks beautiful
yeah Jim Jim 2.0 is a real
thing he's he's a real thing but um yeah
as far as what what what we're hearing
the any inside info so to speak wink
wink that I have is not um go to market
it's it's uh off the Record stuff but
let's just say there is there are some
very ey opening mistakes that occurred
behind the scenes and like I was saying
on the live I did last night myself when
I talked to all these different pipe
hitters who are watch pipe hitters I
love that [__] word I'm gonna start
using that pipe hitters that's [__]
such a good word once once D comto like
started using that like you know they
were all solid pipe hitters I'm like I'm
gonna use [__] pipe hitters yeah that
could go two ways though it it yeah well
unless he was cracking up the first time
he used it on air because and I had to
turn him and say that doesn't mean what
you think it means but um but they there
are some eye openening things some
serious concerns definitely some
security concerns moving forward um that
you know some of these guys and I know J
was really pounding the table on this
you know that there may very well be
some private security to help supplement
what's going on here because the you
know the just the lack of preparation
and the perimeter that that we saw was
insane but um I had a really good call
with with Remy today and who's 12E Navy
SEAL and done all kinds of badass [__]
around the world yeah and um he he he
has heard some things and and seen some
things that that are really concerning
and you know I I think everyone's on the
same page they want to make sure there's
no violence of any sort that occurs
against either of these candidates or
anyone associated with them for the next
100 days especially yeah so that we can
just calm the [__] down as a country
check out this hot take we just had
karaku piped in through Skype and he was
saying that uh if it was he doesn't
believe this was a deep State
assassination attempt he believed it was
just a lone 20-year-old psycho he was
saying that if it was a deep State
operation or any kind of government
agency that was in that was doing this
he said if they failed on the first
attempt they will not try again they'll
take their ball and go home just like
the Bay of Pigs I agree I I I think I
think John spot on about that you like
you had your shot if that's the case I I
don't know but if if that's the case and
that's what some people are saying well
you had your shot and you missed because
now everyone's awake to it yeah
everyone's like oh oh [__] they like
like you know the number of people who
were inserting a quarter into the Alex
Jones was right again jar I mean that's
that's a big [__] jar right now yeah
it's a big [__] jar critical of a lot
of a lot of stuff Alex Jones does and
says but I'm one of these guys like yo
when when people are right I'm gonna
shout that from the rooftops and Alex
Jones was absolutely 150% right on this
issue theyve been saying for years
they're going to come after Trump
they're going to try out kill him state
government is coming after and and like
globalist you know whether or not you
know it was actually who he thinks it
was that's Up For Debate but nonetheless
you know they we we watch we we watch
the guy come
legitimately at a minimum of two inches
from being the next France Ferdinand
yeah which how about Eric Prince still
in my line I love that bro I I used your
line three or four times during this
podcast with Matt but I I credited you
every time oh thank you brother you're
welcome I appreciate that I always
always credit your show too we love it
inspiration anyone listening go watch
the Julian Dory live stream that he did
35 minute [__] rant no camera
switching straight from the [__] top
right off the top of his head no notes
just freestyled 38 minutes of fire on
this whole thing and it was beautiful it
was gorgeous and um I mean I I don't
think that uh I've heard a better take
than from what you said it seems like it
seems like everyone's watched your video
and then just kind of like went you know
riffed off that and and went from
everything that you know all the
thoughts that you had and all the
perspectives that you had you called all
of your contacts your military contacts
and your you know FBI people that you've
had on your show and got all their
opinions and condensed it into one very
uh unique perspective and it was [__]
great dude yeah I appreciate that a lot
man Danny called me came out okay I just
I I I just called Matt Cox and said hey
we got to go do a
podcast that's it baby because call him
the 18 me and Matt just me me and Matt
Cox just watch a bunch of Tik toks and
then uh develop an opinion off
that I'm
disagree this
situation watching Tik Tok oh God all
right bro well we're about to wrap up my
my phone's on like 2% but I'll hit you
up in a little bit SS later
I think I figured out the audio oh we
did all right here we go Demolition
Ranch guy responding to the shirt here
we go wow 1.4 million views in 4 hours
can't
imagine so as a lot of you guys know um
and we
were shocked and Confused to to find
this out the shooter who tried to
assassinate Trump was wearing merch from
my channel wearing a a demol I Ranch
t-shirt and that sucked to see
that yeah that was that was rough so
this this t-shirt we also own a t-shirt
company um it's based out of this my
hometown right here and my friends work
there and we we make these shirts we
print them here in Texas and ship them
all over the world uh I've seen my
shirts in every continent
I got a picture like two weeks ago of a
guy wearing my shirt in
Antarctica and
so we don't vet the people who buy our
shirts obviously it'd be impossible to
just like Nike doesn't vet who buys
their shoes I wish I could I would love
to keep people like that from buying
wearing being associated with that
article of clothing like I wish I wish
he couldn't get a
shirt but it happened
and I think the difference in you know a
gunman wearing a pair of Nike shoes and
a gunman wearing my t-shirt is this
brand is much more personal to me than
Nike is to its Executives and so to see
my name next to the shooter's
name oh it sucks and I wish I wish we
could keep that from happening so no
matter what side you're on politically
none of us want violence this channel
was never meant to
incite violence or hate it never has it
isn't and it never will be a channel
that does
that I don't want any violence or hate
anywhere around me I have a wife and
little kids I want them to be safe and
secure forever and the videos I put out
I want to make sure that is the same for
everyone who watches my videos that they
aren't in any more danger because of my
videos of course and I know you guys
know that I have 11 million subscribers
who have been watching me for over 10
years and know that I am uh not that
kind of person this is mostly for the
people who are just tuning in to
see if I am a guy that is trying
to make people do stuff like that so I
am not uh obviously I don't have to
explain that to you guys who know me but
I I feel like I might need to say that
for those who don't it's crazy that's an
unfortunate situation the guy was just
trying to look like a trump supporter
and wearing like a American shirt
there's probably guns on the shirt or
whatever he was trying to blend in and
unfortunately he picked a [__]
Demolition Ranch shirt I don't think
anyone blame that blames that guy you
can't you can't blame him no but it
sucks for the guy though well cuz people
are going to but but the people that are
reaching out are just idiots of course
yeah the people reaching out to
say people trying to make a story out of
nothing it's just yeah they're they're
probably like mainstream news media type
people trying to make a story out of
this [__] and get clicks I forget what
was the guy what was the chick's name
that was on I forget the guy's name he's
got kind of a conservative show and she
goes on there and she's like why do you
think uh Neo the some Neo-Nazi or
something uh subscribe to your channel
and he's like are you joking like what
are you talking about like you know what
I'm saying like people are so out of
Dodge man like how does that have
anything to do with me
so it's crazy man every you know the
majority of like the mainstream media
the [__] you see on television to see
the [__] that you see being written
about in like the mainstream
Publications like New York Times and
Washington Post or all this these are
all opinions and um pieces that are
written by people who live in [__]
New York and Los Angeles right right
that's that's the consensus of that
that's like you know what's happening
when it's all coming from those places
and they think that their opinions are
more important than the people living in
the rural parts of America right oh yeah
cuz just like they say like all Trump
supporters are stupid uh Stupid poor
white people right
exactly like um I mean I I have a
college education right and I think
people are figuring that out too and
like we were talking about earlier with
the whole Civil War thing like Cal like
I think that guy made that video about
Civil War and like California would be
against Texas they would cut off
California I don't know I think
California I mean it's obviously it's a
blue state but those are like condensed
into like the cities of LA and S
Francisco the from my experience the
majority of people that I know from
California they're like either
right-wing or they're like closet
conservatives like closet conservatives
I know that it's like that weird weird
little bubble of La where it's like you
have to be liberal to be able to fit
into that industry and to keep your job
and to keep getting work you know well
what what you have to understand that
the the he's basing it on the fact that
like hey like the whole state like the
State the government the state
government is at War you know what I'm
saying so if you're a farmer in
California you're saying I disagree well
that doesn't mean that the the National
Guard isn't going the California
National Guard isn't going to go to war
you know they're saying that hey the
people in charge of that state people in
charge the National Guard yeah are going
to go after like that has nothing to do
with like there there's always going to
be the population yeah doesn't matter as
much yeah there's tons of people that
are going to be you know that are going
to be caught within the state saying I
disagree with what Florida is doing but
I'm trapped within Florida and there's
there's a civil war do I up my uproot my
entire family and try and move to a blue
state right now or there just hunker
down right so but that's what his if you
watch that video it was a great it was
it's it really you could watch on the
way home I think it's like 45 minutes
You' be super I think we actually you
reached out to him I tried to reach out
to this guy M tr get him on here too we
tried to get Tyler to reach out to him
Tyler can't get in touch with yeah and
Tyler's you know acious dude's a [__]
ghost did you see by the way did you see
the video of [__] Jack Black yeah
yeah yeah but I I didn't I I I Jack
Black was like saying find a better
shooter don't miss next time yeah yeah I
mean I I like I could barely hear what
he was saying but I read the comment uh
the comments that were basically that's
what he was saying it was just like you
know the pro here's the problem when you
surround yourself with Yes Men you know
you start to think that everything you
say is clever and funny and that
everybody agrees with you yeah that's
why these people when they go on like
Fox News or CNN or they go to these
panels and they start spouting their um
you their propaganda and when people
push back they're like shocked of course
they're shocked right I have a I have a
a group of 20 people that I surround
myself with that I talk to nearly every
day and they tell me I'm everything I
say is wonderful they never push back so
the moment they pushed back they
immediately typically crumble or they
start going you know they get upset and
they start calling people names or they
you know that's that's Jack Black I'm
sure he surrounds himself with a bunch
of people that say he's just wonderful
and everything he says is hilarious and
every they agree with everything he says
and then he says it in the wrong form
and it's like oh wow that didn't that's
not coming off well yeah it was Kyle
glass not Jack Black Kyle is his partner
and Tenacious D oh okay oh Kyle is the
this guy that's that guy yeah okay Jack
Black wasn't Jack Black just recently at
some uh like political convention uh
they hired him they hired him at uh he
super left they hired him at like one of
those one of those conventions and uh he
was like he got up basically talking
about how great Biden was and how
[__] Trump was Hitler yeah these
people say these things just who's the
other guy dairo oh yeah Dao what a
meltdown that was like what a colossal
[__] up like it's the same thing you
surrounded yourself with all these
people that think you're wonderful and
then you say hey I'm going to go and I'm
going to hold a press conference and I'm
going to do this and say this and then
it back fires on you you
know oh this is his video is that what
this is I don't know oh come on is it
this thing what does he say turn the
volume up hit the little volume button
bottom left of the screen there not only
the city but the country and eventually
he could destroy the world know what are
you doing but we vowed we would not
allow
terrorists you hear I the city a lot you
hear the f what are they saying and
that's why it's so weird that Donald
Trump is just across the
street cuz he doesn't belong in my
city I don't know where he belongs but
he certainly doesn't belong
here we New Yorkers used to tolerate him
when he was just another grubby real
estate Hustler masquerading as a big
shot it's all right you can PA it's it's
the same thing you know whenever most of
these guys come up like they never have
anything of substance to say it's always
like he's Hitler he's a racist he's he's
a clown he's uh he's a liar he's it's a
give me some ex examples bro yeah well
that's that's the thing it's like it's a
weird psychological thing where they can
use Hollywood to
propagandize politics like if we can get
a bunch of famous actors that make a lot
of money and that everyone sees on
movies all the time to say something
then people are going to fall in line
because if these people think this then
we should think this but since when are
when is the prerequisite to be an actor
to be a a [__] thinker right or to be
like some political expert or like a
policy expert your job is to pretend to
be other people like that's exactly
that's what their job is exactly that's
exactly what it is to pretend to be
other
people and Trump is I mean his life has
been like is he a textbook narcissist
yes yeah but he's got some issues he's
got a few issues some issu
he's got a few issues but he's been
[__] buying and selling and building
real estate his whole life hotels
casinos golf courses he I mean say what
you want about the guy or put whatever
your politics are like I think it's
undeniable at this rate to say that the
guy doesn't love America oh no I like I
I have no doubt in my mind that he loves
America there's no doubt in my mind yeah
you know he's but you know
people boy people don't like him what's
a fun what's so what I love is that when
he goes out and he's like it's funny
when I was a
Democrat you people loved me you know
what I'm saying when he was a in New
York when he was a Democrat for 40 years
and he was donating to all the
Democratic parties they loved him all
the candidates loved them and then he
said I think I'm going to run as a
republican I feel like I've more those
types of values um suddenly he became
the you know oh you're a bastard well
when I was writing you those checks you
didn't say that
dude they got so many ways to try to
assassinate him it's scary like there's
the shootings like obviously being
exposed in public areas surrounded by
buildings right that's number one number
two is poisoning is he just [__]
eating anything people are giving to him
or are you like super paranoid now you
got to have the secet Secret Service Che
that's got to be the worst way to
[__] die right in a [__] room
where no one else is there you ate some
pudding and you just [__] fell over
where did you get the guy listen you
could just poison McDonald he loves
McDonald's right right right you know
that's how I want to go out though like
has a guy that has to taste test the
food and make sure it's not poison yeah
I need a secret service listen you saw
that tubby little uh little chick that
was in front of him yeah she'll she was
cowering behind him yeah she'll she'll
try something if you said hey would you
you want to you want to take eat a
quarter of my myig hey lady take a bite
of this Whopper she's never seen a
Whopper that she didn't
she wasn't willing to try oh God and
then you know they got tons of other
like truck bombs poisoning the food
there's there's so many other ways to
kill the guy but airplanes CIA is synony
is [__] is famous for assassinating
people in airplanes what what about Tak
planes down um I was going to say I I
love uh like is he getting on his
[__] air like like the balls they
circled Washington couple times the
balls he's flying what at least two
times a day I you know granted he's
flying on his own plane but like if I'm
him and I'm flying twice a day across
the [__] country I got my plane
surrounded by cameras I got security
watching the cameras 24/7 to make sure
no one approaches my goddamn plane you
know
like so everyone who gets on the plane
the [__] the whoever if they have I
don't know if they have like a flight
attendant on this private plane or like
the pilots like crazy screenings for
those people every time they get on the
plane to make sure there's no like
suitcase bomb or anything like that you
still you you keep think you have to
understand all of that stuff means that
the that the bomber or the that the
Assassin is willing to die too that's a
huge like yeah true I just there's not a
lot of people are like yeah yeah oh what
yeah you're going to give me $100
million okay give me the suitcase right
that's true that's true I'm going to be
killed like what do you mean I don't
care how much money you give me right um
uh yeah yeah it's it's a surface air
missile I mean blame it on Russia I'm
sure there's there's lots of ways to to
take him out but what once again they'll
probably take their ball and go home I
mean at this point it's just proba it's
too late here it's too late he's too far
in he's too far in let's just say let's
assume that this was some kind of a
coordinated um attempt to assassinate
him and they do take their ball and go
home there's still a lot of crazies out
there like some crazy might still just
get them I mean I think the kid was just
a 20-year-old crazy but you know they're
still and and either this this has done
one of two things it's either for some
of those people it's either had them say
wow look how close this guy got I can do
this or they've said I'll never even get
close enough and it so you know what I'm
saying so it may some people it may have
embolden them and some people that may
have said oh I'm not I'm not willing to
be killed like yeah this kid he had a
perfect shot couldn't do it and end up
dead no not interested right so yeah I
think he probably in November he wins
you know and that's it he wins and Biden
steps down and he the wars I huh and we
end all the wars and happily ever after
I think he probably stops [__] with
uh Iran he probably uh where else are
are we got Iran we got the um Israel
Gaza Israel Gaza he's I mean that's
already kind of you know on autopilot
he'll probably give him some money and
then um and then just put his support
behind them and then uh as as far as uh
Ukraine is concerned I think he's he's
probably going to have a a very harsh
talk with Putin and say Hey you know
look like you keep what you've got turn
around you got you know look let's he's
probably just kicked the ball down the
road like you're not doing anything on
my watch or then we're just going to put
a bunch of troops and then Putin will
say well then we'll we'll nuke you and
he'll say right let's do it yeah let's
go and then Putin's going to go [__]
never mind I'll just keep what I've got
and I'll you know and basically Trump
kicks the ball down the line and hopes
that he can fortifi they can fortify it
over the next four years and hold what
they've got that's it like I think
that's probably because I don't see him
going in and telling Putin get this get
all your [__] and go home and Putin
being okay with that but I think he says
hey you keep what you've got like this
isn't going to happen on my watch and
I'll I'll throw all the American troops
in there because [__] NATO yeah and then
Putin goes [__] okay you know that's the
best case scenario that's really the
best case scenario yeah yeah I mean if
anyone's got a better chance to to solve
this thing diplomatically I think I
think he's gonna be incentivized to do
that and I think he probably can do it
even though the funny thing is even
though Biden has made it abundantly
clear he doesn't mind getting into a war
right you know he just he's just limited
on what he's doing it's very it's very
you know like and it's very um yeah not
only that he he he's he's actively
avoiding that like they there was
multiple peace talks early in this whole
War where there was like there was this
uh a victory Ukraine had over Russia
early on an early battle where Russia
was on their heels and one of the top
Generals in in the military was
basically saying like Now's the Time to
go to the negotiating table we can
actually negotiate a [__] ceasefire
here and and end this thing and Biden's
White House was like [__] off no way
yeah that's a mistake John Mir shimer
talks about this endlessly um so I don't
know man but I think uh I think if
anyone's going to solve these world
problems I think me and you are going to
do it right here in this podcast so they
need to get a hold of us and get us in
Washington get us in the White House two
guys that know about 3% of what's really
happening how long did we just do like
that was like three-h Hour podcast man I
thought it was going to be an hour but
we went it was a two and a half I'm two
and a half that was close that was close
two and a half that's great cool man
well uh thanks for Matt that was this
was uh this was
fun shout out shout out to your YouTube
channel oh yeah yeah I got a YouTube
channel killing it it's it's doing
pretty good you're blowing up dude it is
doing pretty good was getting you're
doing how many podcasts a week now um
well I mean we're posting three
sometimes four but you're recording how
many four that's nuts dude sometimes
more you are a [__] machine listen I
had one
today I had one today I don't know you
know the guy and I've had a couple of
these where like the the person you know
they're like oh like uh you know hold on
I'm going to smoke a [__] fatty
before I I I start and you know I'm like
uh you know cuz you're texting let's say
it's a not in person but let's say it's
a um a remote well sometimes they are in
person like the guy gets stoned in the
car and they show up and they sit down
and then it's like like I don't know why
these guys think that's a a good idea I
guess cuz they've never smoked they've
never got you know whatever they've
never smoked some dope sat down and then
tried to tell their story obviously
they're usually hanging out with their
friends watching TV uh well when you sit
down and try and start thinking
you know um chronologically and telling
your story it breaks down you realize
right away like this is a bad idea bro
like so they're not all Bosak like Bosak
will take like a ton of stuff a ton of
[__] drugs and be perfectly fine well
not the first podcast he didn't hear I
gave him two gummies and he was blasted
oh was he Oh I thought he did he was I
thought he was kind of fine you were
like oh this guy's not going to be able
to move well no even you said after his
first podcast you're like he was all
over the [__] yeah he was he was but
he was still semi functional normal
person wouldn't be able to tellep this
guy's texting me telling me like he's
going to hold on give me five minutes
I'm going to light up one real quick and
I went yo bro I said uh that's probably
not a good idea I said I've had multiple
people who have done that you know
they've been doing this for a few years
now like it never works out he's like oh
I'm just [__] around I'm not going to
do that just give me five minutes and
then he gets on there we went an hour
and I'm
going hey and here's the thing like I
saw your paperwork so I've in your
paperwork like I know what you're
telling me is is true that you you did
get this much time all of these things
did happen you were charged with these
crimes I've I've read the the
um um sorry the Articles and but when
I'm asking him questions he's like I you
know he's like yeah bro like I got
arrested like like like a b like I don't
know what he said eight times seven
eight times seven eight times and I went
I said oh I said like well like for what
like you know like a bunch of stuff like
what you're like I don't man like a lot
of different things like I anyway so so
then and he just kept going and then
there was another time where he was like
oh I'm making this I was making this
much money and I remember the article
had said he had made several million
dollars and I was like yeah I was like
so what kind of what are you spending
that money on he's like
um you know I stop like you know we're
like I mean I don't really know the bar
is low huh and I'm like you don't you
made5 or $6 million and you don't know
what you spent any of it on did you buy
cars like I don't I don't know I mean
and I was like like I've read the
articles like you know what I'm saying
it's like he was so [__] up that we I
kept thinking he'll get better I finally
just said listen bro we got to stop and
I I I put it on pause I said listen I
said how do you feel you're doing right
now you said that yeah I said how do you
think and he goes and he goes um not
good man not good he I mean he said like
I I listen I know you told me not to but
I got [__] up beforehand I was super
nervous an a lot of anxiety I'm anxious
and I um uh and I went yeah I said
here's the problem I'm asking you
questions that you should know the
answers to and you're like uh I don't
know like you don't know you don't know
that when you were at the counter and
you used a credit card and the guy said
I got to call the manager whether or not
he called the manager uh yeah bro like I
can't remember you can't remember
whether this is a huge deal
uh and I go I mean bro like I'm sorry
but I I said I don't think you're
bullshitting I read everything I saw I
know what's what's going on I know you
got to rest I know what happened I said
but you got to do better bro and he goes
um yeah I uh and he just next thing you
know you see him moving boom he just
disappeared he just exited disconnected
wow so you're going to post it now now
people now people are going to want to
watch it no it's horrible bro and the
worst thing is is like it it would be
different if I thought you're you're
[__] bullshitting me but he sent me
all this stuff and I've read all the
stuff and there were newspaper articles
and he's in them and there's he sent me
like he sent me like his paperwork from
being arrested and what he was charged
with and his indictment like this is
true you just got so overwhelmingly
[__] up and you were so anxious you
could not tell your story right and so I
so I texted him I said hey bro I don't
know what happened I think you just
disconnected I said look I get it I said
do you want to re you want to reschedule
this he's like bro let me just think
about this like I I don't know I
shouldn't have got [__] up I'm so
embarrassed I'm so sorry you know he
apologize and I get it but it was just
like you know like these guys they come
on the like I said the bar is low and
this guy has an amazing Story by the way
like it's it's a dark with guys on my
channel love dark web fraud kind of
story oh man guys do you think you're
ever going to venture out of True Crime
and cover some more stuff you know I did
once or twice I've done some like UFO
stuff right and and and like a few of
them did really well like probably some
one of my top 10 videos U is probably
like a UFO video yeah but um but then I
did a few more and then they start very
quickly they start dropping it DRS the
they don't they don't get a lot of views
and then um you know every time I
venture out like I'll venture out every
once in a while some guy's got a crime
story like it's almost like he's trying
to work in his Crime Story like I I you
know like he did 6 months MH or what
else are you interested besides true
crime stories I just like what do you
what do you like what other kind of what
other type of stuff are you like
interested in talking about or um you
love talking about China we've done a
bunch of China
podcasts I feel like I'm over
China and I I just don't you know if
luckily I T typically have a little bit
more knowledge than the person I'm
talking to so you can semi sound like
you know what you're talking about but
the problem with China too is that like
there's so many things going wrong right
now you know and it's it's just getting
worse and worse like I'm just interested
in in like it's such an interesting time
to be alive right now it really is dude
and you know here's maybe it's not even
that interesting Danny maybe it's just
that the access to the information is so
overwhelming at this point like it
probably always this interested
interesting back in the 70s and 80s and
the 90s when I grew up they just the
there's no internet there was no
internet I don't have a clue what's
going on three states now it's just you
wake up you [__] grab your phone and
you're instantly drowning in information
it's it's insane dude I'm also super
interested in like this whole how like
like the in Japan you know that there's
just there's tons of just abandoned
houses and and their their their like
their working class is disappearing and
all these people are old like there's
nobody to replace these jobs and and
that's happening everywhere it's
happening in Japan it's happening here
it's happening yeah so I'm like it's Neo
feudalism dude it's insane like what's
going to happen like what's going to
happen what's going to happen when
there's not enough people in Japan to
pay into their social security style
system to pay the people that are
retired like what's going to happen when
yeah same thing with here like what
happens when there's not enough people
to pay in to support the people that
have been paying in right I mean I you
know they're like oh it's going to
collapse like they're not going to let
it collapse but they basically just sent
enough money to Ukraine that you could
have fixed it right so I know they'll
fix it but it's like how and you know so
those things worry me but I'm
unfortunately I'm not smart enough to
come up with the solution or have you
don't give yourself enough credit bro
you're super smart everyone I talk to
they talk they brag about how smart you
are I'm just just because I'm a con man
they just don't know they don't know I'm
fooling them no you're smart like I I
what's going to happen bro yeah I don't
know and also do you see that they're
talking about there's like reports of
the military times talking about like
bringing back the draft and there's lots
of there's lots of countries like France
and Germany they're talking about
bringing back the draft nobody nobody
wants to be in the military anymore
they're protesting I think it's getting
so bad they're protesting about it
they're like seriously contemplating
bringing back dra the draft but there
are other countries where you have to
you you have to go in for two years or
four years or six you you have to and
here we're Listen People when my mother
would would tell stories this is during
World War II she was a little kid in
World War II like six seven eight years
old she remembers when they put out
flyers and the newspaper came out and
they said listen any extra pans that you
have that they're going around they like
and this is in like government like they
had a guy they had guys in a little
outfit it's it's the government but like
they'll get like a truck right we're
bringing a truck around through all the
city neighborhoods in these blocks in
this area for the next week if you have
extra pots and pans bring them out
outside and give them to us they're
building Liberty ships out of them could
you imagine if right now they said hey
we're going through your neighborhood if
you have extra metal pans donate them
we're not buying them you're giving them
for the war effort and you know what
they had so many of them they didn't
know what to do with if they did that
now nobody'd give anything hell no
they'd be like oh [__] you it's like you
don't realize how good you have it they
didn't have it one tenth as good as we
have it now and they're giving
everything they can we got four pans but
we can live off of one I got three kids
to feed and I got one pan [__] it give
the other three pans I want to help
build a ship to help defeat Nazi Germany
and now people wouldn't they wouldn't
donate a dollar no you know it's so so
sad and they won't here's the real
problem is like with the US like I don't
think you'll I think the real problem is
and this is what really sucks is that
the US is so isolated we'll never be
invaded does that make sense yeah yeah
we're surrounded by two oceans right
like we we've got the best you know we
we have the best geographical setup
right so we're always going to be in a
great position the problem is
economically we may be devastated and
that's what China and Russia and
everybody's working on right absolutely
um but but like in Europe they've been
invaded so many times at least they have
that fear you know and so that I forget
his name he's a a British politician
where he's like other countries aren't
they're not teaching their children to
hate their country you know like they're
not in Russia they're not preaching to
hate Russia and hate the government of
Russia and the country of Russia like in
the United States you're being raised to
hate your own country yeah so I I just
think that it's just it's just so sad
when I see it goes to what bu Deonte has
said on this podcast many times is we
need an enemy to be able to unite it's
like the 911 thing it's like that 911
showed us you know a real existential
threat and people banded together like
no other after 911 and we haven't had
anything like that we don't really have
an enemy so we fight ourselves those
countries over there in Europe they've
been through so much hell in the last
100 years that it's like I mean even if
you're even if you're like in your teens
there's like you have your relatives
telling you about it you have the
epigenetic [__] fear built into you
of of what's been happening in that part
of the world you're surrounded by other
countries and other foreign governments
and militaries all the time and you see
these atrocities every decade or so
there's some atrocity where one country
is invading another one and then they're
wiping out an entire race or trying to
and you're like you know like the serbs
you know when they invade you know
Croatia and the serbs and then they go
They're going around with hit squads
like you know it's possible in a couple
couple hundred miles or you know Kil
away or whatever you say whatever they
forget what the system but Kil yeah it's
it's not far away like oh my God that's
only two countries away like that's a
that's a 5 hour drive and I could be
there and right now they're they've got
hit squads going around killing
croatians like but it's we're so far
removed that we just think that could
never happen so the idea of saying hey
there's a draft and people freaking out
like you can't make me this you can't
like I'm not doing that like bro it what
are you going to do if they show up on
our borders the problem is they're not
going to show up on our borders and the
pro yeah that's the problem and if there
was a draft like the problem is people
are waking up now to how much [__]
is wrapped up in these wars and how it's
just fueling this military industrial
complex and growing it's just a
mechanism to grow our GDP and dominate
the rest of the world and install
democracies in the rest of the world
like we can't just worry about ourselves
did you see um so why would you want to
be drafted into this [__] right I
mean I I hear you there's what are you
fighting for you're fighting for some
billionaires like and you're fighting
for this [__] fake democracy of
people running running this [__]
brain dead puppet that we don't know who
the hell's running it but they obviously
their moral standards aren't what they
used to be in this country with the as
far as leadership goes did you see this
did you ever watch the series
Fallout no oh my God
Stephen oh [__] yeah it's awes I heard
it was great though right it's so you
know what I think you told me about this
before I meant to watch it and I just
didn't it is it's it's it's it's so I
feel so it sucks I don't get to spend as
much time watching good shows anymore
what's great is that it's everything you
just said it's like it's like capitalism
and the industrial complex gone wi like
in the 50s like what if it didn't taper
off you know instead it's it goes wild
and then it gets to such a point where
they start a nuclear war because they
built these bunkers and we can survive
the war MH I mean it's it's Insanity
like the right but the problem is the
bunkers it's going to be all the
billionaires and the [__] Joint
Chiefs of Staff and all the all the
politicians flying around in their jet
with their [__] pocketbooks full of
all this lobbying money and while us the
the the workingclass blue collar
podcasters like us make it we don't make
it blue collar he just said blue
collared uh podcasters not you man you
just went up at the tax bracket I know
what's going on with you Matt you're not
classified as Blue Collar
anymore but anyways thanks again this
was a great podcast you got to watch
these these I know I don't have time man
I'm raising two kids I got [__] I I
don't have the luxury of time that you
and Julian have your wife is Raising
those kid to study all this [__] and
spend all this time my wife's raising
the kids she is raing she is raising the
kids but I got a I'm busy too man I do a
lot of [__] with my kids I'm not a
[__] absent
father um when are you going to cut up
that Sizzle reel we just got done
filming it Matt give us a break he has
to Pace himself for a week yeah I need a
weekl long breather I we fil for 45
minutes we have to hire an editor so if
you're an editor out there and you're
watching this we are now hiring an
Editor to cut up a Sizzle reel for a one
of Matt's books that were turning into a
pitch for a television series or a
documentary whatever either way hit us
up a series no not a series might be a
four-part deal who knows more like a doc
more like a doc do like a limited doc
Series yeah yeah all based on the story
of you meeting epim deoli from war dogs
in prison and his scam against Warner
Brothers to B sue them into Oblivion
coning you into writing the book the
lawsuit the whole thing super good and
we've been filming it for the last few
months we interviewed uh de Ry we
interviewed Pete Rini we interviewed FBI
agent Jim diorio we interviewed you yeah
who else uh Pac house yeah I already
mentioned pack house did I okay yeah
yeah he was one of the first I thought
you said deoli sorry oh no no yeah we
didn't interview deol we interviewed Pac
house yeah but yeah we we want to put
together a Sizzle reel it should be
super cool but we need a talented
talented talented Editor to help us out
yeah for what would you me three five
minutes three minutes five minutes
Sizzle 5 minute Sizzle yep could be
banging and I've actually already
written out a
semi uh you know uh Sizzle so kind of a
loose leaf kind of like how I thought it
should go how we can edit it do yeah but
you know whatever it comes whatever
somebody comes up with something better
I mean I'm a novice I don't really know
what I'm doing as far as a Sizzle is
concerned but yeah but we've definitely
got the footage beautiful thank God
Steven was here to to shoot it and yep
Steven did most of the work St said set
it all up Steve was cinematographer and
uh Danny drove us to Miami I just was
the driver pretty
much all right tell everyone where they
can find your YouTube channel follow
your podcast all that stuff let's wrap
it up I gotta get the [__] out of here
it's almost 9 o' listen to be honest
with you you guys can do
better I be honest it's Matt Cox inside
True Crime if you have some time check
it out four podcasts a week Matt a
goddamn Workhorse knocking it out we'll
link it below good night everybody see
you